Who are you here for?
I'm here to see Tawan.
Is this her house?
Ms. Tawan doesn't live here anymore.
Then...
do you have her contact number?
I don't. I'm really sorry.
♪ I want you to know my heart for once ♪
♪ My gaze is me hoping for you to listen ♪
♪ To what my heart feels about you ♪
♪ But you never pay me any mind ♪
♪ No matter how much I try ♪
♪ You close your heart and keep ignoring me ♪
♪ The closer we are, the further it feels ♪
♪ Never once ♪
♪ Did you notice what my heart was feeling ♪
Now that you're by yourself,
the rain won't stop.
♪ When I look at you, my eyes say it all ♪
♪ Waiting only for you to pay me attention ♪
It's best you come home with me.
♪ My heart yells every day
But its voice never reaches you ♪
♪ I want you to know how long I've kept this in ♪
♪ Do you have any idea ♪
♪ As each minute goes by ♪
♪ How much my heart wants to say I love you? ♪
♪ All I know is my heart's stubborn ♪
♪ Even when you ignore me
There's pain but also love ♪
♪ That has never lessened ♪
♪ The closer we are, the further it feels ♪
♪ Never once ♪
♪ Did you notice ♪
♪ What my heart was feeling ♪
♪ When I look at you, my eyes say it all ♪
♪ Waiting only for you to pay me attention ♪
♪ My heart yells every day
But its voice never reaches you ♪
Can you promise me that
from this day on, no matter what happens,
you won't forget who you are?
Keep up your grades.
Follow your dreams.
I believe that your perseverance
will lead you down a good path.
Stay strong.
I'll always be rooting for you.
I promise you I will do my best.
I will realize my dreams.
Spotlights will shine on me.
And when I'm successful enough,
when every pair of eyes are fixed on me,
you will see me then,
and I will get you back.
Failed!
Go back to training.
I no longer trust your company.
I'll find my daughter's bodyguard myself.
As far as I know,
I don't meet your criteria at all.
I don't think we need to
look for another company, Dad.
Looking forward to working with you,
Ms. Bodyguard.
We have additional rules.
Always stay in
the bodyguard's line of sight.
How far is the line of sight?
Am I in your sight now?
♪ The closer we are, the further it feels ♪
♪ Never once ♪
♪ Did you notice ♪
♪ What my heart was feeling ♪
♪ When I look at you, my eyes say it all ♪
♪ Waiting only for you to pay me attention ♪
♪ My heart yells every day
But its voice never reaches you ♪
♪ I want you to know how long I've kept this in ♪
♪ Do you have any idea ♪
♪ As each minute goes by ♪
♪ How much my heart wants to say I love you? ♪
♪ When I look at you, my eyes say it all ♪
♪ Do you have any idea ♪
♪ As each minute goes by ♪
♪ How much my heart wants to say I love you? ♪