♪ You're the only one in my heart ♪
♪ Even if you never know ♪
♪ I'll keep watching over you ♪
♪ I love you more than words
but our path isn't easy ♪
♪ I just need you to believe in me ♪
♪ I'm weak for your lips ♪
♪ And the kiss upon my forehead ♪
♪ Every action conveys these words, you know? ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ Use the feeling you know ♪
♪ And you'll love so deeply ♪
♪ Can you feel my love? ♪
♪ Please know that I love you ♪
It's because you're like this…
that I can never get over you.
While the divorce isn't finalized,
I can sleep with you anytime I want?
There are plenty of ways
to make it look like we're in love.
Then let's do all of them.
What exactly are you making?
Mom!
Oh! Oh!
-Oh!
-Stop. She's going to misunderstand.
Open the door right now!
Give her some space, Ging.
If I did, I'd lose to that woman.
Yes, Mom?
I'm feeling a little dizzy.
Can you take me to the hospital, Runch?
Of course.
I'm on my way now.
My mom's not feeling well.
I need to check on her.
I might be home late, okay?
Hm?
That hag is sick?
Mom, where are you?
-She's here.
-Are you okay?
I don't think I need a doctor anymore.
I'm feeling better now.
Anyway, do you remember Maylin?
Maylin?
Maylinya, Samorn's daughter.
You used to play together all the time as kids.
Oh!
Right, I remember now. Maylin.
It has been so long.
It really has.
I didn't think
we'd run into each other again so soon.
She just got back from the States two days ago.
Since you're already here,
why don't you stay for dinner?
She has so much she wants to ask you about.
You're both in law, after all.
-Uh…
-Please?
Pretty please?
All right, Mom.
-Eat up, dear.
-Thank you.
Maylin starts work next week.
Why don't you give her some advice, Runch?
I'd be happy to, Maylin.
Working in law takes a lot of attention to detail.
But more importantly,
you have to see clients as people, not just cases.
Sometimes what they don't say
matters more than what they do.
That was really well said.
I'm glad we met again.
Could I get your LINE ID?
Sure.
Here.
Got it.
Thank you.
You should eat too, Runch.
Okay.
Neen?
Neen.
Open the door. I'm home.
What is it?
Did you bring me dinner?
Who says I bought that for you? I didn't.
But it's all my favorite food.
You waited for me, didn't you?
No, I didn't. Why would I?
Here.
Eat something first.
I'm not hungry.
But your stomach…
says otherwise.
I said I'm not hungry.
Don't be hangry, okay?
Come on.
Come downstairs and eat with me.
If you won't come on your own…
I'll carry you instead.
So? What's it going to be?
Here.
-Your hot fried rice.
-Thanks.
-Let's eat.
-I'm digging in.
Eat up. Try this too.
You must be starving.
Mm.
So what was wrong with your mom?
Her blood pressure.
Blood pressure?
She needed you to rush over for that?
At first, I was going to take her to the doctor.
Which means…
you didn't go?
Why not?
She felt better, so we didn't need to.
I knew it.
She wasn't really sick.
She just wanted an excuse to see you.
You can never tell when she's playing you.
She's still my mom, okay?
Whether she was actually sick or not,
I still had to make sure she was okay.
Right. Such a perfect daughter.
Let's eat, okay?
Well?
Aren't you going to check your phone?
No, I want to focus on dinner with you.
Nothing else matters right now.
Okay.
Okay, Mom.
Tomorrow's my day off, so I'll go visit them.
All right.
Bye.
Where are you going?
My mom said my grandparents miss me.
She told me to visit them if I have time,
so I'm going tomorrow.
Perfect. I've been missing them too.
I'll come with you.
Who invited you?
I'm going alone.
How are you supposed to go alone?
What if your grandparents ask where I am?
What are you going to say?
That we're getting divorced?
They'd be shocked.
Let's just go together, okay?
It's settled. I'm off to work.
No, Runch…
Runch!
What are you doing?
Packing your stuff. Obviously.
You don't have to do that.
They're my things. I can pack them myself.
I just want you to do less work.
Thanks.
But don't do it next time.
I'll still do it anyway.
You always forget something when you pack.
That's not true. I can pack just fine.
I just…
might forget sunscreen or something.
Exactly. That's why I'm packing for you.
How nice…
What's that?
Hmm?
Nothing.
Oh really?
Go pack your own stuff. I'm taking a shower.
What if…
I want to shower with you?
No.
Just go.
-Out.
-But I'm not done packing for you yet.
I said I can do it myself. Go shower too.
You sure you can handle it?
Is this a good time, Maylin?
I wanted to invite you out for a meal
since it's a holiday today.
Runch will be joining us too,
so you should come.
I'll send you the location later, okay?
Thanks, dear.
Who was that?
Oh…
that was Maylin. Samorn's daughter.
We met her when she was little.
Ah, I remember now.
The cute little girl
who used to follow Runch everywhere?
That's the one.
Didn't she study abroad?
She did. She just came back recently.
She even brought me gifts yesterday
right after she landed.
Such a sweet girl.
She's beautiful inside and out.
What a shame…
What do you mean?
It's a shame she came back too late.
Otherwise, I would've wanted her
as my daughter-in-law.
Don't be ridiculous!
What's wrong with that? I was only thinking.
Then keep it as a thought.
Try not to commit sins, okay?
What are you talking about?
Trying to break up someone's marriage is wrong.
I'm warning you.
Hmph! Such a know-it-all. But I don't care.
I should call Runch.
MOM
Just answer it already,
or she'll keep calling nonstop.
Yes, Mom?
Runch, let's have lunch together today.
I can't today, Mom.
What do you mean you can't?
You're busy all day?
Can't you spare a few hours for me?
I really can't today, Mom.
Maylin's coming too.
She wanted to see you.
Sorry, Mom. I can't make it.
I'm on my way
to Neen's grandparents' country house.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I already invited Maylin.
She's going to be disappointed if you don't come.
Are you far already?
Can't you come back first?
You can head there after lunch.
Ugh, that's impossible, Mother.
We're already more than halfway there.
Turning back now would just waste time.
You put me on speaker, Runch?
Yeah, Mom.
I'm driving.
We really can't make it, Mother.
Just tell your precious Maylin.
Buy her a lollipop or something to cheer up, okay?
I'm hanging up now.
Runch needs to focus on driving.
That little brat… She actually hung up on me?
Neen,
why are you mad at me?
I'm not mad.
Come on. You're clearly upset.
I can explain about Maylin.
So you do know why I'm upset. Then why ask?
I can tell…
-You're jealous.
-I'm not jealous.
Why would I be? We're getting divorced anyway.
She's just my mom's best friend's daughter.
We used to play together as kids.
That's all.
Your mom clearly doesn't see it that way.
She practically set the two of you up.
Neen…
Don't be mad at me, okay?
If your grandparents see this,
they'll notice right away.
They'll worry.
They want to see us happy, remember?
Hold my hand when we go in, okay?
Grandpa? Grandma?
Oh my, look who came all the way out here!
I missed you so much!
You're always such a sweetheart.
I missed you too.
Hey, let me hug her too!
Goodness, you're so impatient.
You've gotten so skinny.
Have you been eating properly?
Or is Runch making you stay thin like a model?
Hey, I didn't ask her to do that.
I eat just fine.
And I'm perfectly healthy, so don't worry.
Runch,
it has been a while, hasn't it?
You've gotten even prettier.
Thank you.
What about me?
You know you'll always be the prettiest to me.
I missed you both so much. Are you two doing well?
-We're doing well.
-Yeah, we're good.
Grandma asked what we want for lunch.
I'm good with anything.
Okay, I'll let her know.
Want to go for a walk? The weather's nice.
Sure.
It has been a while since we did that.
We used to go on walks together all the time.
Okay.
Then let's do it after lunch.
Say what you want,
but you just want an excuse to spend time with me.
I know you too well.
We'll eat first, then go for a walk.
Come on.
Do you ever want to live like my grandparents?
You wouldn't be happy living out here.
I'm asking about you.
Would you want this kind of life?
I like being with you.
Nice try.
For you, milady.
Wow. Not even store-bought. You're so cheap.
Sorry, I'm not Ms. Peeracha Pacharathakul,
buying a giant bouquet for Employee of the Year.
You liked it though, didn't you?
Back then…
I felt a lot of things.
Congratulations on Employee of the Year.
And your promotion too!
Thank you.
But how did you know?
Well… my last name is Pacharathakul.
Pacharathakul?
You have Mr. Aphichet's last name?
That's my boss…
That's right.
Mr. Aphichet is my uncle.
Is it a nice last name?
Want to use it someday?
Wait. This award and promotion…
You didn't pull strings for me, did you?
We're not even dating yet. Why would I?
And if we were dating? Would you?
No.
If you don't believe me… try dating me and see.
What did you just say?
I'm asking you out.
Huh?!
Date me.
Hold on. Wait, what?!
Are you nervous?
Aren't you?
We've been getting along pretty well.
Well… yeah, that's true.
Then we should date.
Fine.
I'll give you some time to think about it.
I've already decided.
Yes.
Wait… Hold on!
Stop.
Someone might see us.
Fine.
But now you owe me a kiss.
Next time… I'm not holding back.
♪ And you'll love so deeply ♪
♪ Can you feel my love? ♪
♪ Please know that I love you ♪
You remember that?
I never forget…
anything about you.
Come on, let's go inside.
My grandparents are probably waiting for us.
Are you shy?
What? Why would I be shy?
You're blushing.
It's hot outside, okay?
Stay here if you want.
What's the secret to staying together for so long?
There's no secret formula.
Every couple has their own style.
You just have to be patient with one another.
Sounds simple, right?
But for some people, that's hard.
I agree.
Relationships
are built on lots of little things.
Your grandma and I went through a lot
before we got here.
We fought.
We disagreed.
We cried together
more times than I can count.
Your wedding last year
was only the beginning.
Like I said,
patience matters.
If you're honest and patient with each other,
a lot of problems can be worked through.
Patience gives you time to think
before you speak
or act,
instead of letting emotions
make things worse.
So between the two of you…
who's more patient?
Probably him.
You see,
I had quite a temper when I was younger.
Then what made you become more patient?
Hmm…
probably his handsome face.
Same here.
No wonder we're family.
Every time I look at Runch's pretty face,
I go soft immediately.
Seeing the two of you like this
makes me really happy.
I hope you stay in love
and grow old together.
Help me move these roses into the pots.
Can you do it?
Of course.
I used to grow plants all the time
before I started working.
Good.
Then I'll leave this to you two.
-Got it.
-Okay.
I didn't know you were into plants.
Back in university,
I loved going to plant markets
and bringing plants home.
But once work got busy, I stopped.
You know white roses are my favorite, right?
Of course.
Do you remember why?
I don't know.
Because they're pretty?
They represent pure love,
graceful love,
eternal love, and new beginnings.
That's so cheesy.
Eternal love?
There's no such thing.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
What?
Is there something on my face?
I'll wipe it off for you.
You're so pretty.
Even with dirt on your face.
All good.
Get all of it off.
Did you?
I'll clean the rest later. Just…
It's fine now.
♪ In the moments when we look at each other ♪
♪ Even if I don't say it out loud ♪
♪ Deep inside, I only care about you ♪
♪ Love is so magical ♪
♪ Even though sometimes I don't treat you right ♪
♪ And there aren't many sweet words ♪
♪ But I want you to know that ♪
♪ My life partner will always be you ♪
Grandpa! Grandma!
We finished planting the roses.
Anything else you want us to help with?
This thing is huge.
How are we supposed to wash it?
I know a way.
I didn't know you could wash it like this.
It's actually kind of fun.
You can let go now.
If I let go, you'll fall.
Let's stay like this. It feels nice.
Okay.
Oh!
Hurry, take a picture!
Quick, send it.
HOW'S IT GOING, MOM?
Perfect.
Did you get the photo, Kae?
I did, Mom.
I really hope your plan works.
It has to work.
I'll make sure those two
change their minds about the divorce.
I'm sure they have to feel something at least.
We're really counting on you, Mother.
Honestly, we also don't want them to divorce.
It breaks my heart every time I think about it.
I could understand if they were divorcing
because of disagreement,
but divorcing because of someone else…
I just can't accept that.
We've tried everything we can.
When they told us, all we could do was respect it.
But we don't want that to happen.
Looking at the photo,
if they stay there another two weeks,
they might actually reconcile.
Mm.
Leave it to us.
Just wait and see.
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ Use the feeling you know ♪
♪ And you'll love so deeply ♪
♪ Can you feel my love? ♪
♪ Please know that I love you ♪
I'm sorry Runch couldn't make it today.
She's busy with work.
It's okay, Auntie. I understand.
That's typical of an attorney.
You barely get any time to rest.
You're so understanding, Maylin.
That's very sweet of you.
I've admired Runch ever since we were kids.
She always looked so cool,
no matter what she was doing.
I actually studied law because of her too.
She told me
she wanted to become an attorney someday…
and she really did it.
Mm.
So I wanted to follow in her footsteps.
Sounds like you really admire her.
I do.
Maylin…
can I ask you something honestly?
Of course.
You like Runch, don't you?
Auntie…
You can tell me.
These days, women liking women
isn't unusual anymore.
I understand.
I do.
I've liked Runch…
for a long time.
Here, eat more, dear.
Thank you.
Runch, come here for a second.
Sure. What's wrong?
Come here.
Neen's in the shower, right?
Yes, she just went in.
Why?
We have something important to talk to you about.
Something important?
Neen's birthday is coming up in a few days.
I know.
We want to surprise her early
while she's here.
So she can take her mind off things
and really relax for once.
It has been such a long time
since we've heard her laugh like before.
Please help us, Runch.
You're the person who knows her best.
Of course.
I'll handle everything.
Mm.
Neen is very lucky
to have someone who loves her this much.
Let's make a plan.
And don't let her find out.
Got it.
This is good.
Oh, thanks.
Try this too.
Neen,
your grandmother and I
need to stop by the temple for a bit.
Can you drive us there?
Of course. I'll take you.
Runch, can you stay
and look after the house while we're gone?
You don't need to do much.
Just clean up the dishes for us, okay?
Sure.
I'll take care of everything.
Perfect. Then we'll head out after this.
Sounds good.
Now eat up, okay?
Eat a lot.
Runch?
Where are you?
Runch…
What's all this?
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Happy early birthday.
Make a wish first then blow out the candles.
Your grandparents won't be back tonight.
They're staying over at a friend's house.
Mm.
They told me too.
Which means…
it's just the two of us tonight.
Mm.
So…
what should we do then?
It's beautiful out here.
I've never really looked at the stars here.
I know.
That's why I brought you here.
I used to love stargazing when I was little.
But these days, I barely even look up anymore.
Oh?
Runch…
did you see a shooting star?
It's really--
♪ In the moments when we look at each other ♪
♪ Even if I don't say it out loud ♪
♪ Deep inside, I only worry about you ♪
♪ Love is so magical ♪
♪ Even though sometimes I don't treat you right ♪
♪ And there aren't many sweet words ♪
♪ But I want you to know that ♪
♪ My life partner will always be you ♪
♪ I'm weak for your lips ♪
♪ And the kiss upon my forehead ♪
♪ Every action conveys these words, you know? ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ My love is in these soft whispers ♪
♪ You have to feel it with your heart ♪
♪ Our touches will make you understand ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ Use the feeling you know ♪
♪ And you'll love so deeply ♪
♪ Can you feel my love? ♪
♪ Please know that I love you ♪
THREE YEARS AGO
The sunset's beautiful.
Still not as beautiful as you.
Your lips are sweet.
Oh? Have you tasted them before?
How would you know?
Not yet.
But I kind of want to now.
I want to find out if they're really sweet.
Today's officially our first day together.
So… may I kiss you?
♪ I'm weak for your lips ♪
♪ And the kiss upon my forehead ♪
♪ Every action conveys these words, you know? ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ My love is in these soft whispers ♪
♪ You have to feel it with your heart ♪
♪ Our touches will make you understand ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ Use the feeling you know ♪
♪ And you'll love so deeply ♪
♪ Can you feel my love? ♪
♪ Please know that I love you ♪
Runch and that new employee
have been getting a little too close lately.
You made me feel like
there's a whole side of you I don't even know.
You crazy minx!
You've ruined everything!
You're the one who did that.
What now? Are you trying to find Runch a mistress?
I did all of this to protect you.
I won't let anyone hurt my wife's feelings.
No matter who it is.
Not even you, Mom.
♪ Living with pain and love ♪
♪ Living while waiting and losing hope ♪
♪ A voice inside my heart says enough ♪
♪ But another voice asks me to endure ♪
♪ I stay because I love you, you know? ♪
♪ I still believe in the love between us ♪
♪ Please let us go back to how we were ♪
♪ I don't know if our love is just impossible ♪
♪ Or if there's a reason for all of this ♪
♪ And that reason is you don't love me ♪