Tawan's single. She's not dating.
Really?
Where is she now?
Asleep. Her people are taking care of me.
You know, I'm still excited.
What about you? Are you okay?
Not really.
Because she got hurt, right?
Yeah.
I feel bad for her. Getting hurt like this.
Hey, she's working as your bodyguard,
so she has to do her job.
Besides, if something happened to you,
your dad would totally kill her.
Ugh, we just reunited a few days ago
and there's already trouble.
Hey, anyway, does your dad know?
Of course not.
I don't want him to know.
He'd made me go home for sure.
Well, that's true.
At least you're unharmed.
Your dad probably won't do anything to her.
Honestly, I'm so confused right now.
On one hand, I'm happy to
have her around, taking care of me.
But on the other hand, when I see her get hurt,
I feel like I don't want her to come to any harm.
You get the picture, right?
And these people trying to hurt me, I have no idea
who they are and why they hate me so much.
And I don't know what's in store for me in the future.
Hey, calm down, Ms. Idol.
Get it together. Focus.
Can you trust anyone else but Tawan right now, Ayla?
You should be glad she agreed to
take this job of taking care of you.
But I'm worried about her.
Yeah, I know that.
You worry about her and love her so much.
I've been listening to this since Grade 10.
Hey, if you're worried about her,
then go take good care of her.
Maybe she'll give in.
Actually, Boss works very hard
to get the company to this point.
And almost all the VIPs who worked with her before
don't want to deal with other companies.
That's true.
We're just telling you, not bragging.
Her standards are extremely high.
If someone mentions her name,
people in the industry know that
she's a perfectionist and doesn't make mistakes.
Being thorough, detail-oriented and observant
leads to successful jobs.
We've been following her principles.
And our jobs have been successful.
Boss told me that
doing our best to protect other people
was a beginning of our duties as bodyguards.
Tawan.
Ms. Ayla?
You should sleep in your room.
Please let me sleep here.
It's better to sleep in your room.
If she wakes up and sees you sleep here,
we'll definitely be punished.