♪ I have a heart and know how to love ♪
♪ Especially when I see you
I keep seeing the scenes ♪
♪ From when we were together ♪
♪ But I keep seeing you in my head ♪
♪ My broken heart hasn't recovered ♪
♪ So I hurt you ♪
♪ Even though I have to
Make myself watch you cry ♪
♪ I hate it but I still do it ♪
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape
But it feels like walking in circles ♪
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
♪ I try not to love you
Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
You're okay.
-Hello, Doc.
-Not okay.
I know you don't wanna see me.
But I still wanna see you.
I have someone I love now.
And I'm gonna marry him soon.
Do it. I wanna know too
if you can kiss a man.
Hey, Lada. Are you wavering?
-No.
-I'm glad to finally meet you.
Oh! "Earn's Eng."
The two of you will become
a new imagined couple.
Today we're an imagined couple,
but in the future,
we might become a real couple.
Don't you have work to do?
Are you hired to work
or gossip about celebrities?
-Yes.
-Just surfing the net.
Wow.
Such amazing chemistry.
Eng and Earn.
So cute.
Hello.
What got you excited, Ms. Rossarin?
I'm gonna go to work.
Sure.
Hey, this is it.
The sky has opened up.
Our problem is getting fixed by the hashtag
"Earn's Eng."
Are you a die-hard fan?
A fan my ass.
I'm happy that actress is
a part of an imagined couple.
So she'd leave Lada alone.
Holding a grudge for our friend?
Or you're not?
I'm angrier than you are.
I'll never forget Lada's life
almost got ruined by that girl.
So this is good news
that she finally got a girlfriend.
-Otherwise our friend would never move on.
-You're right.
She would keep coming back to that girl.
Huh?
What? Huh?
-Why are you tapping?
-No...
Why are you tapping?
-Why didn't you tell me?
-I was trying to.
Hey, Lada!
Hey, you!
Let me drink.
Hey!
This is your favorite dish, Lada, isn't it?
-You're right.
-Hey.
I remember this one is very delicious.
Let's eat. I'm starving.
-Oh!
-Huh?
"Earn's Eng."
By the look of it,
The two of you, Eng and Earn,
will become a new imagined couple.
Today we're an imagined couple,
but in the future,
we might become a real couple.
VOICE CALL
TODAY - UNREAD MESSAGES
Eh?
Hello, Engfah, where are you?
Wow, you returned my message so quickly.
I came out for drinks with Yun
and some crew members.
I spotted someone you want to see in this bar.
So I sent you a picture of her.
Engfah,
do you mind sharing your location?
I'll be right there.
-Sure.
-Okay.
See you in a bit.
Where are you going now?
You just got home.
The guardian spirit only got a glimpse of you
Where are you off to?
Huh?
Suzie?
I'm begging you.
But you just got out of the hospital.
I just wanted to hang out with Engfah.
I won't touch alcohol and...
I'll take care of myself.
Please. Suzie, please. I promise.
Please.
Please, please, please, please, Suz.
I promise, Suzie.
Are you hitting on me?
Oh! I love you the most in the world!
So please excuse me. I'm gonna change.
Bye, Suzie. See you later.
What mood are you in, Doctor,
that got you sit alone quietly here?
Looks like it's not quiet anymore.
Earn's gonna be here soon.
I came by to tell you
in case you wanted to know.
Don't chew me out yet.
I already told her that
she just got out of the hospital,
that she shouldn't come here.
But she insisted she had to come.
Eh, maybe...
when Earn arrives,
she should sit here?
Eh? Where are you going?
A different bar.
This place's not good for relaxing anymore.
Lada.
Have you been waiting long?
Let's find another bar, Tan.
Where? I braved the traffic to get to you.
Stay here.
Uh, I won't bother you anymore.
Enjoy your evening.
Hey,
what did that actress want with you?
Nothing.
One Manhattan.
Yes, coming right up.
Oh, slow down, Mother.
Jeez.
-Your Manhattan.
-Thank you.
Hey, cheers.
Take small sips, okay?
Lada, I said small sips.
-Hey!
-More.
Oh, Lada. Wait a minute. Calm down.
Why are you drinking so much?
This is too much.
Lada, you can't handle this.
Enough, Lada. This is too much.
Enough.
Give it here. Stop drinking.
That's enough.
-Give it back.
-You'll spill it.
No, enough. Stop drinking.
How could you drink this?
I have to go to the bathroom.
I'll let you have only four more.
Then we'll leave.
Okay?
Okay.
That's all you'll get.
Please cut her off.
Sure.
One Pick Me Up.
Yes, coming right up.
Are you here alone?
How many people do you see here?
Only one.
Have you been waiting long, baby?
Hm?
You're drunk. How many have you had?
Should have told me you're taken.
By an actress too.
Pick Me Up for you.
Please excuse me.
Doc.
You're drunk. That's enough.
-Give it back.
-Doc, no, that's enough.
Goodness, she's wasted.
Plus she's alone. It's dangerous.
Suzie?
I'll take care of her.
Go have fun with Engfah.
What do I tell her?
You can tell her whatever you want.
And please take care of her bill.
Come on, Doc.
-Doc, let's go.
-Okay.
-Can you manage?
-Help me.
Goodness me.
-How much?
-Just a moment please.
It's 8,500 baht in total.
Huh?!
8,500?!
Yes.
Where's my friend?
-The doctor?
-Yes.
-She's gone.
-Gone where?
With Earn. But don't worry.
She'll take care of her.
That's the most worrying part.
Yes?
Pay him 8,500 first.
Oh.
Yes.
-You take credit cards?
-We do.
Okay.
Doc, why did you get so drunk?
Doc.
You're very drunk.
How did you get so drunk?
Earn.
Doc.
Where are you off to?
I'm leaving.
Doc!
Stay and talk to me.
I have so many things I wanted to discuss.
But I don't.
What about last night?
Move.
I'm leaving.
Get out of my way.
Good morni--
Huh?!
How did this happen?
Tell me everything.
Don't omit anything.
Well...
It's nothing.
Doc and I used to date.
Huh?!
Used to date?
When?
Four years ago. When I was abroad.
Eh?
When you said you'd dated someone,
you meant Dr. Fahlada?
Then what?
You said you'd broken up.
What was that earlier?
We did. I dumped her.
Goodness!
You dumped her?
Why did you do that?
Back then I was...
Back then I was stupid.
But I realized that now
and I'm gonna get her back.
So this means...
last night
when you found out she was at the bar,
you went there and picked her up,
then you let her sleep here.
Don't tell me
last night
you poked at an old flame until it ignited again.
Why didn't you tell me?
I accepted so many duo jobs with Engfah.
But right now
you have a real girlfriend.
Oh, what real girlfriend? I don't have one.
Doc's still mad at me.
Mad?!
But you two banged.
Doc might have done that
just because she was drunk, Suzie.
Why is your life this complicated?
What now? What about my Engfah?
She'll be disappointed.
She won't be, Suzie.
There's nothing between Engfah and me.
That's true for you.
It might not be true for Engfah.
There won't be anything between us.
I guarantee it.
If you're the woman I'm into,
what would you say?
I don't think of you that way.
That's okay.
I don't mind this being one-sided.
Let's get to know each other.
And you can reconsider
if you can date someone like me.
I already love someone else.
And that person is Dr. Fahlada.
Fahlada?
That dermatologist and socialite?
That's right.
We used to date.
And we broke up because of my own stupidity.
I see.
So what now?
Do you want her back?
I'll help you.
-This one and the next.
-Yes.
Well? Is everything okay?
-Where's Ratee?
Ratee, get briefed on the blocking.
-Come on.
-Yes.
Go over there.
All right, do the dialogue for me.
Uh...
-With low voice?
-For now.
I already told you I wasn't involved.
Liar.
Your dialogue.
You're cunning.
You think I'm not on to you?
Okay. After this, Earn, turn around.
Then Ratee, grab her shoulder.
Gently.
And right away, slap her.
But do it away from her face.
I'll use a camera angle.
Okay? Away from her face.
Got it.
All right, rehearse for me.
Five, four, three, two, action.
I already told you I wasn't involved.
Liar. You're cunning.
You think I can't see through you?
"Not on to you."
You think I'm not on to you?
Wait.
Hey!
Oh!
Did that hurt?
I didn't mean to.
The distance was...
You meant to do that, didn't you?
I didn't, Engfah.
Why would I do that?
Hey, that was just a rehearsal.
Why would you take it seriously?
She's right. You crossed the line.
Or are you jealous of Earn?
So you took a cheap shot.
Jealous?
Why would Ratee be jealous of you people?
-Are you picking a fight?
-Yeah. Bring it on.
I'll fight you. Wanna do sumo? Come on!
Fine, let's go! Bring it on!
-Come on!
-You come first!
Wait, you guys!
It didn't hurt that bad.
You can't let this go.
Trust me, Engfah.
I'm fine.
Let's not fight.
Ek, Earth, let's just do it.
All right, I'm glad you're okay.
Let's start filming. Come on.
Uh...
I'm gonna change it to...
no more slapping.
Okay? No more slapping.
Yes.
Earn, turn around and walk.
And walk away.
-Yes.
-Come on, let's start.
Okay, everyone, get set.
Did it hurt?
Thanks.
Are you ready?
I am.
All done.
Follow the nurse to get your medicine.
Thank you, Doctor.
-I'll help with the buttons.
-Thank you.
Hot Americano, unsweetened,
for Dr. Fahlada.
No.
My order...
is hot latte.
I didn't know you drink coffee with milk now.
I'm sick...
of having the same thing.
Caramel macchiato,
25% sweetened, for Earn.
Engfah?
You remember my order?
Then, your order must be...
Iced latte, 50% sweetened.
Right?
You're so sweet.
You remember my favorite coffee.
I used to work in a coffee shop.
I'm good at memorizing orders.
Look, they love each other.
Doctor!
Oh.
Ms. Ratee.
Are you picking me up for lunch?
Uh, that's right.
Good.
I happen to know this amazing restaurant.
I'd love for you to try their food.
Uh, which restaurant?
You'll Like It.
Of course I'd love it. Why wouldn't I?
Since you're inviting me.
Let's go.
So let me take off my...
lab coat before we go.
Then I'll help you change.
Let's go.
"You'll Like it."
Yes.
You mean it was the restaurant's name?
Why?
Nothing.
I just thought when you said, "You'll like it,"
you were talking about me.
Oh.
You're funny, Ms. Ratee.
Yes.
Let's go.
I'll have to rush back to work.
-Yes.
-Please.
Yes.
Wait for me.
YOU'LL LIKE IT
I can't choose.
I don't know what to get.
What's this? Putting out food
before the customers come?
I ordered your favorite beforehand.
Oh?
Son-in-law eggs.
-Yes.
-My favorite.
I knew it was your favorite,
so I ordered beforehand.
Shall we?
Sure.
I'll get...
this.
This.
Come on, I'll get it for you.
Which one first?
-Try if it's good.
-Aren't you eating?
-I'll let you eat first.
-I'll try it.
Yes, ma'am.
You want a bite?
No?
Thank you.
Ms. Ratee,
the spaghetti here is sublime.
You wanna try?
Yes.
Thank you.
You're planning on fattening me, aren't you?
Your current shape is actually perfect.
Even if you're bigger, you'll still be cute.
Thank you.
Stir-fried glass noodles here is delicious.
I'll get it for you.
-I can do it myself.
-It's okay.
-Hm?
-I'll feed you.
Ah.
Is it good?
So good.
Wanna try stir-fried holy basil?
This is delicious too.
I'll put it there.
For good hygiene.
Thank you.
Eat up.
Food at You'll Like It is so good.
You're right. Everything is delicious.
I'm so full today.
I didn't think Dr. Fahlada
would be this attentive.
She picked a great restaurant.
What about you? You came with Engfah.
You're into her?
Why?
I'm just curious
if an imagined couple on social media
is a real couple.
It's none of your business what we are.
You're right.
Because I'll definitely pair off with Dr. Fahlada.
You're very confident.
Of course I am.
The doctor is good-looking,
talented and rich.
She's perfect for me.
Despite your words, have you asked her
if she's into you?
I don't need to ask.
I can guess from her invitation today.
Why?
Are you jealous?
But then again...
I guess that's all you can do.
Because someone of her level
won't look at someone
of the low-end market like you.
If I'm of the low-end market,
you're of the black market.
But I'm sorry,
no matter how black you are,
I still see through you
that someone like you...
is really like.
Pitch black.
I have your fruits.
Yes.
Earn is sweet.
What do you want?
Just looking for an opinion.
About her.
I don't know.
I heard...
she's the presenter of your hospital.
I thought that was your decision.
It wasn't.
But even if you didn't pick her,
someone else would have picked her.
Because they would get
a presenter who's beautiful,
sweet,
and nice.
Don't tell anyone.
I'm pursuing her.
Please root for me.
Slap me.
Come on, I'm letting you slap me.
How dare you insult me?
I didn't insult you.
I was telling the truth.
Even since you slapped me on set.
You think I didn't know you meant to do it?
I just didn't want to waste their time.
Good. Now you know I hate you.
I despise you.
Fine.
Stop! What are you doing?!
Back off!
Stop! Back off!
Back off! Stop!
Here you go.
Now you know I hate you too.
Why are you wet?
Ratee again, wasn't it?
I think I have to take care of it.
It's okay, Engfah.
I don't want trouble.
Okay.
Let's leave.
If you wanna leave, I'll leave.
I already paid. Let's go.
I'm off, Doctor.
When there's a chance,
let's talk again.
What are you laughing about?
I was picturing the person I tricked.
I couldn't help laughing.
Did you overdo it?
Jeez, she doesn't get people like us.
She's spent all her brain cells
on treating patients.
She won't figure out our tricks.
All the more reason for me to overdo it
so she realizes what's what.
And what about the person who got you wet?
You want me to get her?
That one's not smart either.
I already took care of her.
-Let's go.
-Yes.
A faucet in the bathroom broke.
It got me wet.
A bad faucet...
or bad manners?
What's that?
Check, please.
It was already paid.
By who?
Ms. Engfah.
She asked me to tell you it was her treat.
I forgot my cellphone.
Huh? Cellphone?
Mm.
Ah.
There it is.
My cellphone.
Mm.
Doc?
Did you come for just your cellphone?
Mm.
That's right.
Can't you stay for a little longer?
Hm?
Please.
Why do you want me to?
Well, to accompany me.
Just for a little while. It won't take long.
Unless...
you don't trust yourself.
♪ I want to say that I love you ♪
♪ Love you with all my heart ♪
♪ You don't need a single word ♪
♪ To tell me how much you love me ♪
♪ Your actions let me know ♪
♪ I want us to stay this way ♪
♪ No matter how tired we are ♪
♪ Our hearts are ready to fight ♪
♪ Just seeing love in our eyes ♪
♪ Is enough to make us happy ♪
Hey! Hey!
-Where are you hurt?
-Take her to a hospital!
Calm down.
Our doctor will take care of her.
It's gonna hurt a little.
But I wanna keep getting hurt.
-Why?
-So you pay attention to me.
I heard when you were abroad,
you and Earn lived together?
Did Earn tell you that?
Who do you think told me?
Did she tell you
what we'd lived together as?
She did.
She said you were friends.
♪ Please don't let go of my hand ♪
♪ No matter what, please be right here ♪
♪ Having you here is reassuring ♪
♪ I'm less anxious than I used to be ♪
♪ You're the good love I never experienced ♪