You think you're so pretty, new kid?
You think Tawan accepts your drink
and you're better than everyone else?
You turn your nose up at everyone.
You want a drink?
Here.
I prepared it for you.
But not in a glass.
You'll get the whole bucket.
No. No. Don't do it!
Tawan.
Why did you have to go this far?
I'm sorry. It wasn't meant for you.
It was meant for this new kid.
She just got here.
How could she get this close to you?
I'm the reason, right?
I don't approve of this behavior.
Bullying is contemptible
and unacceptable.
No matter to whom.
It breaks my heart
that I'm not setting a good example.
Tawan, no.
It's not your fault.
You're very good. You've always been good.
It's our fault.
We're really sorry.
-I'm sorry.
Then let this end here.
I'm asking you.
Of course.
You ask, I obey.
We're good.
Huh?
We're good just like that?
Yeah.
Tawan asks, we obey.
Are you okay?
Thank you, Tawan.
For saving me.
You always protect me.
It's like you're my bodyguard.
Bodyguard?
I'm expensive.
Can you afford me?
Can I ask you something?
You love dancing, right?
Yes, I love dancing.
How did you know?
Well,
I saw you...
when you mopped the club floor.
You danced so hard
the floor was clean.
Huh?
Tawan got my gift.
You saw the whole thing?
I saw the whole thing.
I saw you were like...
I'm gonna cry.
You saw everything.
Our school has an excellent dance club.
I think you should join it.
Kendo is too much for you.
No, I like kendo.
I like kendo.
I even love it.
You love kendo...
more than you love dancing?
I think...
that's not true.
Why not?
Do I look that hopeless?
Yes.
Tawan, you're not very encouraging.
Just trust me.
Following your heart...
is always better.
But...
if I'm not in the kendo club,
I won't get to talk to you every day like this.
Of course you will.
You can say hi to me whenever you see me.
Or...
I train here every day.
You can come if you want.
It's a date.
♪ You are the moon in my heart ♪
♪ You make everything ♪
♪ More meaningful every day ♪
♪ I wanna be your sun ♪
♪ Please let me ♪
♪ Be by your side and keep on loving you ♪
♪ You bring light to the darkness ♪
♪ You make me smile every day ♪
♪ You make the lonely nights
More beautiful than they've ever been ♪
♪ Once looked lonely ♪
♪ They're now filled with your shadow ♪
♪ As the light to my heart ♪
♪ You are the moon in my heart ♪
♪ You make everything ♪
♪ More meaningful every day ♪
♪ I wanna be your sun ♪
♪ Please let me ♪
♪ Be by your side and keep on loving you ♪
♪ You are the moon in my heart ♪
♪ You make everything ♪
♪ More meaningful every day ♪
♪ I wanna be your sun ♪
♪ Please let me ♪
♪ Be by your side and keep on loving you ♪