Start
The Secret of Us_EP6_Engsub_HD_25fps
♪ I have a heart and know how to love ♪
♪ Especially when I see you
I keep seeing the scenes ♪
♪ From when we were together ♪
♪ But I keep seeing you in my head ♪
♪ My broken heart hasn't recovered ♪
♪ So I hurt you ♪
♪ Even though I have to
Make myself watch you cry ♪
♪ I hate it but I still do it ♪
\N
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape
But it feels like walking in circles ♪
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
\N
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
\N
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
♪ I try not to love you
Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
See how Engfah and Earn
are so sweet together.
Real kisses, no stand-ins.
Is this fun for you?
So you can just mess with me?
Why are you doing this?
Playing with my feelings.
It's my fault, I'll take responsibility.
Whatever's on your mind, just say it.
I want you and Earn to reconcile.
How's that?
Is it fast enough for you?
I was going to court Earn.
But Earn doesn't like me
because she loves you.
I'm here.
May I sit with you?
Please?
Now that I'm sitting,
can I help with the puzzle?
That's wrong.
It's still wrong.
I was
wrong.
You can punish me,
or
you...
could kiss me.
What's so funny?
Huh?
Is kissing me funny?
No.
Are you really trying to
make up with me?
I'm trying my hardest.
It's no good.
Doctor,
can we start over?
Will you be my girlfriend?
Of course,
my little rascal.
♪ Please don't let go of my hand ♪
♪ No matter what, please be right here ♪
♪ Having you here is reassuring ♪
♪ I'm less anxious than I used to be ♪
♪ You're the good love I never experienced ♪
♪ I will hold your hand like this forever ♪
♪ Don't release my hand ♪
♪ Just be confident that I always have you ♪
♪ You're my one and only ♪
♪ No matter how many obstacles, I will push through ♪
♪ No matter how tough it gets ♪
♪ I want to say that I love you ♪
♪ Love you with all my heart ♪
♪ I’m no longer addicted to coffee, ♪
♪ I’m more addicted to you ♪
♪ My heart is not available now, ♪
♪ Because you’re right here beside me ♪
♪ We see each other almost every day, ♪
♪ My friends ask how I don't get bored ♪
♪ How could that be possible? ♪
♪ Let me clear up the doubt ♪
♪ My partner is so cute ♪
♪ So cute, I could die ♪
♪ It’s okay if people think I’m lovestruck ♪
♪ My partner is so cute ♪
♪ So cute, I could die ♪
♪ What kind of person is this ♪
♪ I want to be with them every day ♪
-Good morning.
-Morning, dear.
Morning.
Congee, ma'am.
Thank you.
You seem different today.
I haven't seen you in such a good mood
for a long time.
Oh, Father.
You always see me as moody,
so when I smile, it's something unusual?
Just curious.
Why, is it wrong to be curious?
Fine.
-Father.
-Hmm?
About the commercial shoot,
I've changed my mind.
I'll do the commercial as you suggested.
You haven't done it yet?
I thought it was already finished.
Oh.
I wasn't ready last time,
but now I am.
Well, that's settled then.
You can decide on these things.
Just don't overwork yourself, okay?
Find some time for Nu.
I feel sorry for him,
he's been waiting for you
for a long time.
Right,
last night I saw the news
about the stock market in the US
it's surging across the board. Look.
Remember the stock I mentioned?
Don't forget to buy it.
See how much it has gone up.
That's true, Father.
Wow!
I'll buy it tomorrow.
I'm going to be rich.
Okay, let's agree on that then.
Why did you change the subject?
About what?
Oh,
I admit it.
I didn't want you to pressure
our daughter about Nu.
If I were really pressuring her,
I wouldn't have let it go on this long.
I'd have made them get married ages ago.
But our daughter doesn't love him.
But it's necessary.
Lada will eventually have to manage
our hospital network.
She needs someone
she can trust to help her,
and the most suitable person is Nu.
Besides, Nu is a good person.
No matter how good or suitable he is,
if her heart isn’t in it,
it’s not going to work.
If you're going to indulge her,
then be prepared to
have a daughter-in-law.
I'm okay with that,
as long as it makes our daughter happy.
Did you know that
more than 80% of office workers
suffer from office syndrome?
Wow, that many?
So how do we treat it,
Doctor?
There are many methods.
She calls her "Doctor" so smoothly.
The change of work environment,
exercise, or alternative medicine.
But at our hospital,
we have a rehabilitation medicine center
specifically to treat office syndrome.
Our equipment is new and
used only in a few places in Thailand.
Hmm, you're making me want to see it.
Can you take me to see it?
Certainly.
Cut!
Hey.
The chemistry is off the charts.
Are you serious, or just joking?
Do you think I have time
to joke around with you?
What? Lada said she wouldn’t
go back to her?
She said she had moved on.
She’s moving on in a circle.
Want to check out
if what I said is true?
Hey, that’s fast.
Wait up!
Don’t worry, because we’re here
to take care of you.
Cut.
That’s a wrap.
Drink some water.
Thank you.
The scarf is beautiful.
Thanks. It’s a gift from my girlfriend.
Ex-girlfriend
or new girlfriend?
I only have one.
Drink some water.
Told ya.
Well, well, well.
Oh!
Dr. Bow, Dr. Tan!
Here to watch the commercial shoot too?
Uh, yes.
I just happened to pass by
and decided to take a look.
So, what’s up?
Yeah.
Well...
It's nothing.
We just made up.
-Really?
Yes.
Ha.
How about dog food?
What flavor do you like?
Liver flavor.
Lada.
Don’t you remember
why you almost didn’t graduate?
Why you almost ruined your life?
Don’t you remember?
And just a few days ago,
you were drunker than a dog.
I'm saying this because
I don’t want to see you
in that state again.
I know you’re worried,
-But...
-But you’re still doing it,
still going in circles like before.
But I love her.
And what about the past?
For everything that happened,
I’ve forgiven her.
You like the liver, right?
Yes.
I like the meat.
Do we have to how, too?
Oh.
Awoo!
Easy, easy, friends, easy.
Guys,
I’m sorry.
I know
I don’t learn from my mistakes,
but I really love Earn.
Just speechless.
Up to you then.
You’ve made your choice.
What can we do when you already
made your choice?
Good luck, buddy.
Yeah.
If you need anything, just let us know.
But if not, I'll say it here.
You’re still our friend.
Even if we don’t agree with you,
we’re still by your side.
Hey,
thanks, guys.
Yeah.
I love you. I love you all the most.
There’s nothing else, right?
Yeah.
Well, that’s it.
I'm off.
Liver flavor, right?
Let’s go, let’s buy it.
Yeah.
Haa...
Another sigh.
Good thing I didn't count.
I'd run out of fingers and toes.
I'm worried about Lada.
I'm worried too,
but she's made her choice.
What can we do?
That's not it.
I mean, I'm worried about that, too,
I don't want her to get hurt.
But
there's something even more concerning.
What is it?
Have the ad crew left yet?
Not yet, ma'am.
But before coming up here,
I saw them still working.
They should be finishing up soon.
Earn, are you done changing yet?
Not yet.
Just a moment.
If you're done,
just toss the clothes out.
I really need to use the bathroom.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Oh!
Doctor!
What is this?
-You startled me.
-Why?
Why?
You startled me!
I've wanted to do this for a long time,
but in front of others,
I was afraid you'd be embarrassed.
Afraid I'd be embarrassed
or are you just not brave enough?
Then let's go.
Where to?
To kiss you
in front of the crew
and announce that
we're a couple!
Earn!
No way.
Why not?
Not without payment first.
Here.
One million,
two million,
three million.
Is that enough?
Not enough.
Still not enough?
Certainly, Earn.
LOUNGE
Mother.
This is
Earn,
our hospital's new presenter.
Hello.
We just finished the commercial shoot.
There's just a bit of interviewing left.
Have you eaten yet, Mother?
We can go grab something to eat after.
No, thank you.
I have no appetite.
Excuse me, Doctor, we're ready for you.
Alright.
Thank you.
I'll go finish the interview then.
Alright.
Oh.
Actually, I'll catch up.
I think I left my bag in the room.
-See you in a bit.
-Yes.
Right this way.
After I helped your mother,
you repay me by breaking your promise?
Why?
Are you desperately in need of money
that you had to return to my daughter?
I love her.
It's up to you to believe it or not,
but it’s the truth.
Even if she is penniless,
I would still be with her.
Clever.
Using love as an excuse
to betray without guilt, huh?
I never broke my promise.
I really did leave her.
You already see that
I stayed away for two years,
never coming near her.
Then why are you back?
Because you lied to me.
You said our love would never be real,
that things would happen naturally.
But it's not true.
Because today,
she's not with Dr. Wisanu.
If I had known,
I would have found another way
to help my mother
and never made that promise to you.
That's why today,
I’m taking back my love.
Here you go.
-Take your medicine.
-Thank you.
Here.
Thank you.
I told you to rest more,
but you never listen.
You work so hard that you got sick.
You're so stubborn.
If I weren't diligent,
would our hospital have grown this big?
Or would you prefer just a small clinic?
If it means having more time with you,
a small clinic would be enough.
Really?
Yes.
I will pass the medical exams
and help you and Father with the work,
so you both won't have to be so tired.
That sounds wonderful.
Do you like the idea?
What did the mail say? Did she pass?
She passed!
You scared me!
She passed the skin medical school exams.
There were so many competitors,
and she scored among the top!
Lada never disappoints me.
Amazing like her mother.
Absolutely, you couldn't be more right.
Come in.
Celeb Today wants to
schedule an interview with you ma'am.
Alright,
ask them for the date.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you hungry?
Just tell me what you want to eat.
I'm hungry,
but I want to go home and eat.
As you wish.
Is something bothering you?
Do you think
your mother will accept us?
Oh, is that all?
Don't worry about it.
It's not a big deal these days,
hmm?
My mom loves me,
and she'll love you too.
She'll understand our love.
Let's go.
Of course it's
Fried Boiled Egg with Tamarind Sauce
and Stir-fried Glass Noodles.
At least we have clear soup.
Are you sure it's edible?
It's your first time making it,
and I don't want to die.
You're underestimate me
Here, taste it and see.
If you're going to die,
you'll die in front of me.
Oops.
Sorry!
I'll stop teasing.
Hmm.
Is that a nod of approval?
It's a nod of
"I'm definitely going to die."
Geez, don't tease me like that!
Okay, okay, I'll stop teasing.
I was just joking.
Okay.
Earn.
Oh, Doctor!
You're up already?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Morning.
I'm ironing your shirt
so you can wear it to work.
But
I'm not working today.
Hmm,
why not? Are you slacking off?
I'm not slacking off,
but I don't have any rounds today.
Ah, you don't have rounds.
In that case,
once I finish ironing this,
I'll go make breakfast for you, okay?
You don't have to go anywhere.
Don't be too nice to me.
Why not?
I might fall even more for you.
Geez,
you're so sweet first thing
in the morning.
Aren't doctors supposed to avoid sugar?
Except for this one person.
Just this one person?
Just one person.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
You sure?
MOTHER
Go answer your phone.
The hospital is probably calling.
Go answer the phone.
Go on.
Hello, Mother.
At 10 o'clock, okay?
Okay.
Don't be late.
Got it. See you tomorrow.
Okay, dear.
Bye, Mom.
My child will not be tainted
by a woman like you.
Earn,
we’re here.
It’s already so late,
what time do you think you’ll finish?
I’m not sure.
The team called me in last minute
because the previous guest
fell ill unexpectedly, I think.
They needed me to fill in,
and I didn’t want to let them down.
Well,
I’d better get to work.
Drive home safely, okay?
Of course.
Thanks for the shirt, by the way.
You’re welcome.
Bye-bye.
Whoa!
Amazing.
Hey,
you know the line-up with Engfah is
now booked for 3-4 months straight?
And your fee is 10 times the usual rate.
You practically don’t have
to do anything else,
just show up and collect the money.
Suzie,
can’t I take other jobs
that don’t involve Engfah?
What?
Why?
Didn't you two sorted everything out?
We did,
but I’m worried about Doctor.
And what about me,
the one who books your jobs?
Oh, Suzie,
you know that there’s nothing
between me and Engfah,
but the people hiring us
want that cute, couple-like vibe.
You get?
I don’t want to mislead them.
Oh, Miss Goody-Two-Shoes,
Look,
not everyone has a rich doctor
for a girlfriend like you.
I can’t be as choosy with work.
Suzie, I’m sorry.
I won’t complain about anything else.
Look, I came here as soon
as they called, no complaints.
Just this one thing, please?
Please, Suzie.
If you don’t, I’ll kiss your cheek!
Eek! Go away!
Are you crazy?
-Will you agree?
-No.
Please?
I beg you.
I’ll give you free facials.
Where?
At Doctor’s hospital.
Glass skin, Korean style,
forever.
Fine.
Doctor.
Are you done?
Why are you still here?
I thought you were going home.
Well, that was the plan,
but when I actually tried to drive home,
I was so sleepy.
I was afraid
I might doze off while driving
and cause an accident,
so I decided to sleep in the car.
But when you dropped me off,
it was just around 7 PM, right?
Were you that tired already?
Well,
I've been working hard lately,
so I'm exhausted.
So...
Are you all done?
Yes, all done.
Let's go home then.
I'm not sleepy anymore.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's go home.
Wrap this around yourself first.
-Let's go home.
Our daughter is grown up now.
Don’t be so serious.
You and I don’t think the same way.
It’s better if we don’t talk about it.
I don’t want to argue.
But it’s her happiness.
It hasn’t even been long,
and she’s already so infatuated
that she doesn’t come home.
I don’t believe that
it’s true happiness.
And more importantly,
Lada has to take over
the business from us.
I can’t let her have any flaws.
Loving the same sex
is not a flaw.
To me,
it is.
Am I beautiful yet?
Not yet. Oops, I mean, always beautiful.
Can I open my eyes now?
Uh-huh.
-Huh?
-Uh-huh.
Your lip balm is quite thick, Doctor.
I’ll wipe a bit off so it doesn’t smear.
How do I look?
You’re so beautiful,
I’m already jealous.
After I finish the interview
with my mother,
I’ll come back and you can be
as jealous as you want.
Sure.
Are you going to work somewhere today?
No,
Suzie is coming over
to practice lines at home.
I’ll be home all day.
Then when I get back,
let’s go find something to eat.
Okay.
If my mother is free,
I’ll invite her too,
so you can get to know
each other better.
Sure.
Huh?
Oh!
Drive safely, my love.
Yes, see you later.
Bye-bye.
Huh? Her mother doesn’t approve?
Yes,
and I didn’t dare tell Doctor.
I’m afraid they’ll argue.
But I’m sure Lady Russamee
won’t let this go easily.
So that’s the hidden issue.
But from what I see,
Doctor isn’t that easily controlled,
She won’t be influenced that easily.
I think so too,
but I realized it too late.
And I've hurt Doctor.
If I had believed in my love more,
we wouldn’t have wasted so many years
and wouldn’t be in
this uncomfortable situation now.
But it made you grow, right?
Otherwise, someone innocent like you
wouldn’t know how to
handle Lady Russamee.
That’s true, Suzie.
So
what do you think
Doctor’s mother will do?
I have no idea.
I just know that
she doesn’t like me
and will probably do anything
to make me stop seeing Doctor.
But this time,
I won’t give up on my heart again.
Are you here to see Lada?
I’m here to see Auntie.
She has an interview,
and she wanted me to be here
to promote our business partnership.
As a businessman,
you don’t miss even small opportunities.
After you.
Aren’t you coming?
Oh,
I forgot that I left something behind.
Please go first.
Nu, you’re here too?
Yes.
Hey,
are you here for the interview too?
Auntie didn’t mention it.
Dr. Wisanu, Dr. Lada,
please come inside.
Everything is ready.
-Yes.
-This way, please.
I understand that the hospitals
in your network, Ms. Russamee,
started from a small clinic, correct?
Yes,
we started as a clinic
in a single shophouse.
Hmm, but now it has grown
into a large national hospital.
Because we work hard
and maintain quality.
And most importantly,
we have a strong partner.
With the good medical equipment
and drugs from Mr. Wisanu's company,
we have been able to grow this far.
It's better to say we grew together.
Without this partnership,
my company wouldn't have
reached this point either.
What is the next step?
Hmm...
It’s better if the next-generation
executive answers this.
I’m just following the policies
that have been set.
In the future, we aim to be a hub
for comprehensive patient care.
No, dear.
You can find that on Google.
We have something more interesting.
Oh, what do you mean, ma'am?
Our future
is good news...
Dr. Wisanu and Dr. Fahlada
are getting married,
and this is the best news.
Wow,
it is a good news indeed
and the biggest news, too.
Congratulations to both of you.
Thank you.
♪ In the end I hurt myself ♪
♪ Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden ♪
♪ I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
You're willing to get married
even though we don't love each other?
If it’s the elders' wish,
I don’t mind.
Why are you doing this, Mother?
I'm not an object that you can do
whatever you want with.
And the person you want to marry,
can you marry them?
I'm begging you.
No,
you have to marry Nu only
because Nu is the most suitable
and appropriate person for you.
What does suitability mean, Mother?
Whatever I deem suitable is suitable.
You have no right to question it.
♪ Please don't let go of my hand ♪
♪ No matter what, please be right here ♪
♪ Having you here is reassuring ♪
♪ I'm less anxious than I used to be ♪
♪ You're the good love I never experienced ♪