♪ You're the only one in my heart ♪
♪ Even if you never know ♪
♪ I'll keep watching over you ♪
♪ I love you more than words
But our path isn't easy ♪
♪ I just need you to believe in me ♪
♪ I'm weak for your lips ♪
♪ And the kiss upon my forehead ♪
♪ Every action conveys these words, you know? ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ Use the feeling you know ♪
♪ And you'll love so deeply ♪
♪ Can you feel my love? ♪
♪ Please know that I love you ♪
Would it kill you
to admit you chose the wrong partner?
I regret marrying you more than anything.
Are you both sure about this divorce?
We've both agreed on it.
No one here knows us.
So why are you being nice to me?
I was just helping an old woman
so she wouldn't starve to death.
Mom!
Runch…
Wait, Runch.
Listen, I really didn't mean it.
You should go home.
Are you mad at me?
Runch…
Peeracha…
Let me treat your wound.
Don't.
I have to.
My mom's the reason you got hurt.
Ow! It stings!
It stings!
Try to bear with it, okay?
I'll clean around the wound first.
Ow, ow…
It shouldn't hurt much, Neen.
I'm just cleaning around it.
I'm not touching the wound.
This might sting a little.
There, all done.
I'm sorry on my mom's behalf.
I'll walk you up to your room.
No.
It's because you're like this…
that I can never get over you.
Ms. Warin, have you really
thought this through?
Filing for divorce means digging up
every part of your marriage.
Some things may hurt more than you expect.
I've been hurting for so long.
I can't even feel anything anymore.
My husband has a habit
of giving me false hope.
He only treats me well
in front of other people.
But at home,
he only spends time with his parents.
It's like I don't even exist.
I don't want to live
with someone like that anymore.
Then let's start with the marital assets.
The house, cars, savings, shares…
everything acquired during the marriage.
Do you have proof
that they were acquired together
or that you shared the expenses?
Yes. But I handled everything on my own.
He never contributed at all.
Assets acquired during a marriage
are considered marital property by law…
They belong to both parties.
Salaries or any assets purchased
or obtained during the marriage,
even if they're under only one person's name,
are still considered marital property.
How about this…
I'll handle everything for you.
You don't have to go through this alone.
Sometimes…
we don't really need much.
We just want to know that the people we love
are on our side.
And sometimes, the one who loves the most
ends up the most exhausted.
You seem to understand
that feeling very well.
Well, it's my job to understand my clients.
Come on, guys!
It's Friday. We should go party.
Same place?
Sure.
But are you paying?
Because if not, I'm not going.
Come on…
Boss.
Our department's going out tonight,
so we were hoping…
you'd treat us.
Does everyone want to go?
Yes.
Everyone has been working really hard lately.
We could use
a little morale boost.
Of course.
Order whatever you want.
But I'm coming too.
You are?
Of course.
I've never joined our department parties.
I want to see how hard everyone
has been working.
I'd also like a chance to talk to all of you…
not just as your boss,
but as part of the team.
See you there, okay?
Yes.
I don't think this is going
to be fun anymore.
Says who?
It's going to be even more fun now.
Come on, everyone.
-Cheers!
Come on, Boss.
Why aren't you drinking?
Drink!
Drink! Drink!
-Yay!
Geez, Boss.
Does your wife only let you drink
smooth, fancy, expensive wine?
One taste of cheap liquor
and you're already wasted.
That's enough, Utt.
Stop trying to get her drunk.
What's wrong with that?
Hey,
fill my glass.
Boss, should we call Ms. Peeracha
to pick you up?
Hey.
If I call her,
she probably won't answer.
Can you call her for me?
I'll dial the number for you.
It's…
It's this one.
I'll call her right now.
Hello?
Huh?
Runch is really drunk?
Okay, I'm coming right now.
Yes, thank you so much. Bye.
Ugh.
Why is she drunk again?
Hey, Boss.
Boss?
Let's be real, okay?
The fancy car you drive,
that ten-million-baht house
in a gated community,
and all those designer clothes…
your wife bought all of them for you?
Wow, Boss.
You really lucked out!
Stop talking like that.
Come on, Boss.
Did the alcohol get to you?
I'm only joking.
Everyone already knows
you're living off your wife.
I see.
You're jealous, aren't you?
Because my wife's hot,
rich…
and she actually loves me.
Unlike you…
You're just nobody…
depending on some middle-aged women
just to climb higher.
And you're terrible at your job too.
All you're good at is sucking up to people.
Say that again.
Want to know…
how people really see you?
You're dragging this department down.
You suck at your job,
all you do is run your mouth,
suck up to your superiors,
and turn people against each other.
Don't push it.
Just because your wife is rich
doesn't mean you can say what you want.
So what?
What if my wife is rich?
That has nothing to do with this.
I'm just telling the truth.
Your wife…
people like her don't really love anyone.
Everyone knows you're just a trophy wife.
-Utt!
-Utt.
If you talk about Neen
like that one more time…
I'll make sure you never speak again.
Damn it!
-Hey, stop!
-Utt!
Hey!
If you ever touch Runch again,
I'll have my uncle fire you.
Runch, let's go home.
You know you can't handle alcohol,
and you still drank.
Right?
But he said
you only let me drink expensive wine.
The smooth kind
that goes down easily.
He said I can't handle cheap liquor.
It's like how I can't eat fermented fish.
He said…
ever since I married someone rich,
I've become too fancy for it.
Come on, Runch.
-Ugh…
-Just sit down first.
I really don't get it. Why?
Why does everything have to come back
to me marrying someone rich?
What's so wrong about it?
They keep saying I hit the jackpot,
but I didn't marry you for money, okay?
Does being married to me
hurt your pride that much?
No…
Then maybe we should hurry up
and get divorced,
so you can finally live
the kind of life you're proud of.
Runch?
I asked Utt if he was jealous of me
because my wife is beautiful, rich,
and kind.
I know he is,
because I have someone like you.
And I know he has been with older women
to climb higher at work.
You actually said all that to him?
I did.
And how would you know that?
I saw them once.
They were all over each other.
You really drank a lot tonight, huh?
You're usually not like this
when you're drunk.
No…
I'm not drunk.
Maybe a little.
But not that drunk, okay?
It's just…
my patience is worse than usual.
Ugh…
Even I'm surprised
at myself.
Mm. That's good.
It is?
You want me to stop being patient?
Because you've been too patient,
we ended up like this.
But I'm not imagining it, right?
You've been a lot nicer to me today.
Neen…
if that's true,
can you spoil me a little more?
What do you want?
Can I sleep here with you?
Please? Let me stay here tonight.
Neen…
I can really sleep here tonight, right?
Just go back to your room
if you're going to keep asking.
I guess I won't ask then.
I'll stop asking.
Thank you for picking me up.
And…
for letting me sleep in here.
Thank you so much.
Are you done? I'm going to sleep.
Whoa…
Neen.
Do you really have to put
a bolster between us?
Just go to sleep already.
Not even a little…
What are you doing?
Hugging you, obviously.
Just let me hold you.
I won't do anything else.
Let go.
No.
I said let go.
Nope.
Nope?
♪ In the moments when we look at each other ♪
♪ Even if I don't say it out loud ♪
♪ Deep inside, I only care about you ♪
♪ Love is so magical ♪
♪ Even though sometimes
I don't treat you right ♪
♪ And there aren't many sweet words ♪
♪ But I want you to know that ♪
♪ My life partner will always be you ♪
♪ I'm weak for your lips ♪
♪ And the kiss upon my forehead ♪
♪ Every action conveys these words, you know? ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ My love is in these soft whispers ♪
♪ You have to feel it with your heart ♪
♪ Our touches will make you understand ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ Use the feeling you know ♪
♪ And you'll love so deeply ♪
♪ Can you feel my love? ♪
♪ Please know that I love you ♪
You're only having coffee?
You're only having coffee too.
I'm not really hungry.
I'm still full…
from last night.
Pervert.
How am I the pervert?
I was talking about dinner last night.
What were you thinking?
Go to work already.
Wait…
Hmm?
Do you want to have lunch together?
We should only eat together
when it's necessary.
Have I already used up all your kindness?
As long as we don't fight to the point
it affects our mental health,
that's good enough for me.
I see.
As for last night…
we hadn't been close like that in a while.
It's only natural it happened.
So we'll just treat it
like we both had a good time.
Does that mean…
while the divorce isn't finalized,
I can sleep with you anytime I want?
That kind of thing still needs my consent.
If you want it but I don't,
then it's not happening.
Then whenever you feel like it,
you can just call me.
Or make the first move like last night, okay?
See you at lunch!
If you guys hadn't stopped me,
I would've hit her back last night.
I don't care if she's a woman.
Geez, Utt…
What?
She thinks she can do whatever she wants?
She humiliated me in front of everyone
like I'm nothing.
What,
just because she has connections
and a rich wife,
she thinks she's untouchable?
Hey, keep it down. Someone might hear you.
I don't care!
I'm telling you,
she was lucky I wasn't that drunk.
Otherwise--
Otherwise, what?
I heard everything you just said.
I'll say this once.
Don't talk about me behind my back.
Say it to my face.
Be a man.
Starting today,
if anyone has an issue with me,
come directly to me.
This is a workplace,
not a street market for gossip.
And one more thing…
if you're better at gossiping than working,
I'll have to reconsider your position here.
Since you think
I'm only here because of connections,
because I have a powerful backing,
because my wife's family owns this company…
then I'll make use of the resources I have
for the sake of the company.
Let's see who's actually working…
and who's dragging everyone down.
This is never-ending…
Come in.
Your lunch is here.
You're really sneaky,
bringing lunch up here like this.
How so?
Afraid I'd refuse to eat with you?
That's right.
So you're forcing my hand.
Here.
Have some.
If this makes people think
we're still in love, then fine.
There are plenty of ways
to make it look like we're in love.
Really?
Then let's do all of them.
You're serious?
Not that kind of all of them.
Too obvious?
Then…
Hey!
I'll settle for this.
But now…
I want to kiss you for real.
We're in Thailand, remember?
Even if we're married,
kissing in public isn't appropriate.
I miss when we were abroad.
We could kiss anytime, anywhere.
Come on.
Go back to your seat.
Move.
Yes, Mom?
I will.
Okay.
Everything okay?
My dad isn't home today,
so my mom wants me to stay over.
Are you telling me,
or hinting that I should go too?
If I asked… would you come?
Ugh!
Seeing her would only ruin my mood.
I figured.
Hold on…
If I don't go,
your mom will probably be too happy.
I've changed my mind.
I'm coming too.
You mean…
you're coming with me?
Yeah.
What?
I can't come?
She hasn't seen her daughter-in-law in days.
She must be dying to see me.
You two always fight whenever you meet.
Wouldn't it be better to avoid each other?
What, scared I'll verbally take her down?
Neen…
I'll do whatever it takes
to make that hag miserable.
Here you go.
Thank you so much.
What did you order?
It's not often I get to stay
over at your mom's,
so I thought I'd cook something for her.
What are you even going to make?
I'm not telling you. It's a surprise.
You'll see soon enough.
Neen, maybe you should cover up a bit.
No.
I like it like this. You like women
who dress like this, don't you?
I don't like any women dressing like that.
I only like you like that.
Hey, wait for me!
Hello, Mother.
I thought you were coming alone.
I actually told her to come alone,
but she's so persistent.
Why would she be?
She comes here all the time.
That's never been an issue.
Oh, there's always an issue when we're apart.
She just doesn't say it to you.
She only tells me.
How could she admit
she can't be away from her wife?
That would just upset you, Mother.
I didn't expect both of you,
so I didn't prepare enough food.
That's completely fine, Mother.
I'll be your chef for today.
I promise you'll love it.
What's going on?
What exactly are you making?
Can you tell me now?
Not yet.
Go sit with your mom.
I promise it'll be unqiue.
Shoo, go on.
She won't tell you what she's making?
Nope.
She's not planning to poison me, is she?
Neen isn't that kind of person, Mom.
Hah! She hates me more than anything.
You really think I don't know?
And I know you hate her too.
Neen?
-Neen!
-Honey!
What is going on?
Why are there frogs in my kitchen?!
I was going to make
spicy stir-fried frog for you,
but I accidentally dropped the container
and they got out.
What should I do?
Look.
Mom!
Oh my…
Mother?!
I've got them all now.
Thank you so much.
-Please release them somewhere safe.
-Of course.
Mother…
I'm really sorry.
Looks like spicy stir-fried frog
is off the menu.
You did this on purpose.
No, Mother.
I really wanted you to try it.
Frog is actually very good for older folks…
high protein, low fat, and rich in nutrients.
Good for brains and nerves.
It also strengthens bones and immunity…
so you won't die too soon.
You…
rude, disrespectful!
Didn't your parents teach you anything?!
They did.
They taught me to be polite
only to people who deserve it.
And you're not one of them.
Runch…
Runch,
you can eat with your mom.
I'll go upstairs first.
Come up when you're done.
I've got a little treat for you.
Why didn't you say anything?
Mom…
I don't even know what to say anymore.
And I'm tired of it.
So you only listen to her now and not me?
Mom…
what do you want to eat?
I'll order it for you.
I won't eat anything. I don't want anything.
Neen…
If you're here to lecture me, don't.
I don't want to hear it.
Just hear me out…
What are you--
Oh, Runch… oh god…
Please stop…
Neen, enough already.
What? But I don't want to stop yet.
What are you doing?
I'm going to make your mom go deaf
from my screaming.
Since she loves imagining things,
I'll make she go crazy this time.
Neen…
Stop. She's going to misunderstand.
-Come here.
-Whoa!
Ugh!
Runch, stop it… Ah--
Neen, enough.
What are you doing to my daughter?!
Neen!
Open the door right now!
Open it!
Leave us alone, Mother. I'm-- Ow!
Runch, don't bite me! That hurts!
Open the door, Neen!
Open it right now!
Ow! You always bite me, Runch!
It hurts! Ow!
Hey, stop it.
♪ I'm weak for your lips ♪
♪ And the kiss upon my forehead ♪
♪ Every action conveys these words, you know? ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ My love is in these soft whispers ♪
♪ You have to feel it with your heart ♪
♪ Our touches… ♪
Are you having fun?
But right now,
you're getting yourself into trouble.
You know that, right?
Mm-hm.
I told you two to make up, not hook up.
Hey, watch it.
Why? Didn't you two…
last night?
You already know what happened.
So, did your hag-in-law know
what you and Runch were doing in that room?
Of course she did.
I was loud on purpose.
She probably couldn't sleep all night.
I was gone for one night
and you couldn't sleep?
Don't be ridiculous.
I couldn't sleep
because there was a demon in this house.
A demon?
What demon?
That spoiled brat stayed over
with Runch last night.
And she…
she…
she did shameless things in this house.
You saw them?
Of course I didn't see them! I heard them.
All night long…
she kept moaning Runch's name.
"Oh…"
"Ah…"
I nearly had a heart attack.
I think the most shameless thing here
was your behavior.
You eavesdropped them
on their private moment!
I wasn't trying to!
I was worried about our daughter.
Worried… or curious?
Curious about what exactly, Pong?
What would I even be curious about?
I was afraid that woman
was putting some kind of spell on Runch.
I just came back from a meditation retreat
feeling peaceful,
and now you've reminded me of something else.
What?
Our daughter has her own life, honey.
We don't own her.
We gave birth to her and raised her,
but we can't live her life for her.
Who she loves…
is up to her heart,
not you.
-But--
-I know you love Runch very much…
but it has made you controlling.
That leaves her exhausted and uncomfortable.
If you keep this up,
you'll only push her farther away.
She's an adult now.
She gets to choose her own happiness,
not the one you choose for her.
Give her some space, Ging.
I'll never do that.
If I did, I'd lose to that woman.
THREE YEARS AGO
Here's your shirt.
I already washed it. Thank you again.
You're welcome.
Next time, be more careful with your coffee.
I will.
Ms. Neen?
Yes?
What is it, Ms. Runch?
Are you free today?
If you don't mind,
I'd like to treat you to a meal as thanks.
But it's okay if you're busy.
Who said I'm busy?
If you want to treat me,
I'm not saying no.
Now that we know each other better,
let's stop being so formal.
Big Sis Runch.
You're younger than me?
Of course I am.
Little Sis Neen…
Do you like that?
Depends on who's saying it.
If it's you…
then I like it.
Actually, there's something else
I want to call you.
What is it?
Beautiful.
You're really beautiful, Runch.
Thank you.
I like you.
I mean… I like beautiful women.
I see.
Well…
I'm glad you like me.
ONE NEW MESSAGE
Morning, beautiful.
Don't forget your favorite coffee today.
♪ I love you more than words
But our path isn't easy ♪
♪ I just need you to believe in me ♪
Got it.
♪ I'm weak for your lips ♪
♪ And the kiss upon my forehead ♪
ONE NEW MESSAGE
Have you had lunch yet, Neen?
Not yet. I'm enjoying your attention first.
♪ My love is in these soft whispers ♪
♪ You have to feel it with your heart ♪
♪ Our touches will make you understand ♪
Sweet dreams, Runch.
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
You too, Neen.
♪ And you'll love so deeply ♪
♪ Can you feel my love? ♪
♪ Please know that I love you ♪
I'm so happy to see you again.
Here.
Aren't you going to check your phone?
No, I want to focus on dinner with you.
Hold my hand when we go in, okay?
I can tell you're jealous.
Why would I be?
We're getting divorced anyway.
You like Runch, don't you?
Auntie!
Let's stay like this. It feels nice.
♪ Living with pain and love ♪
♪ Living while waiting and losing hope ♪
♪ A voice inside my heart says enough ♪
♪ But another voice asks me to endure ♪
♪ I stay because I love you, you know? ♪
♪ I still believe in the love between us ♪
♪ Please let us go back to how we were ♪
♪ I don't know if our love is just impossible ♪
♪ Or if there's a reason for all of this ♪
♪ And that reason is you don't love me ♪