♪ I have a heart and know how to love ♪
♪ Especially when I see you
I keep seeing the scenes ♪
♪ From when we were together ♪
♪ But I keep seeing you in my head ♪
♪ My broken heart hasn't recovered ♪
♪ So I hurt you ♪
♪ Even though I have to
Make myself watch you cry ♪
♪ I hate it but I still do it ♪
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape
But it feels like walking in circles ♪
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
♪ I try not to love you
Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
What do you study here?
I'm studying management. What about you?
I'm studying medicine.
Please date me, my stubborn girl.
Lada must break up with that girl
and marry only the person I choose.
Hello, ma'am.
If you break up with Lada, I promise
to give your mother the best treatment.
Let's break up.
From this day on, let's not see each other again.
I missed you, Doc.
Is this her?
The presenter who will be
in the commercial with me?
That's right, Doctor.
This is Earn, Sanitada,
the number one rising star right now, Doctor.
If so, I'm pulling out.
Suzie, this photoshoot came out amazing.
Of course. The model is gorgeous.
You would look great no matter
how cheap the cameras are.
Do you want anything for that compliment, sis?
No!
-Hey.
-Hm?
I'm just thrilled for your popularity.
Did you know the other day
some hospital contacted me
to get you to be their presenter?
A famous private hospital.
One of the best in the country.
And you'll be in a commercial with the owner.
She's beautiful, rich, talented.
Everyone wants to work with her.
She is...
Ta-ta-tan!
Dr. Fahlada.
I'm not taking this job.
You have to. I already said yes.
The pay is seven figures.
Deals can be canceled.
But I won't be taking jobs
related to this hospital.
Why not? Give me a reason.
I can't tell you.
Anyway, please call and cancel for me.
Hi, everyone.
Today we're honored to talk to Dr. Wisanu,
a young doctor
who runs a medical device business
and the future love partner of Dr. Fahlada,
the heiress to a famous hospital.
Oh, am I right to introduce you like that?
Actually you're only half right.
I own a medical device business, but...
I'm not anyone's love partner yet.
Eh? What about the gossip among the insiders?
Well,
I've been pursuing Dr. Fahlada for many years
but...
she hasn't given in yet.
So if anyone has any pointers, I'm all ears.
You might be unaware
that before she went abroad,
she'd already started dating Dr. Wisanu.
Suzie,
I've changed my mind.
I'll take this job.
You gave me your word.
If you go back on it, you'll be a pariah.
I'll put it on your calendar.
What's the heck is going on?
First you played hard to get,
refusing to take this job.
Now it's Dr. Fahlada playing hard to get.
Hey.
Let me as you honestly.
And answer me honestly.
Did you ever have a problem with Dr. Fahlada?
Why did she pull out and refused
to be in this commercial with you?
No.
I didn't have a problem.
Are you lying?
I'm not.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
If it wasn't you, then who?
The director?
Or someone in the crew?
No idea. I don't know either.
-Are you lying?
-Earn. Suzie.
Please come with me.
Someone wants to talk to you.
I'm in a bad mood today.
I don't wanna talk to anyone.
The hospital's executive wants to talk to you.
Of course I'll go.
Why didn't you start with that?
But what do they wanna talk about?
Let's just go.
Please take that.
You have to put yourself in their shoes, Lada.
The entire crew came here at first light.
to wait for you to shoot this commercial.
But you pulled out
in the last minute without reason.
It's wrong.
I agree with Bow on this.
You crossed the line this time, Lada.
Who said I didn't have a reason?
So what's your reason?
Or...
you're worried about fame?
Oh.
It's possible.
Lada is what they call...
an introvert.
If Lada's an introvert,
am I what they call an innocent?
Someone as seasoned as you, Tan? An innocent?
Hey, Bow,
you called me "seasoned"?
Your sharp tongue
is the reason you're still single.
-Tan, you're so foul-mouthed.
-What?
Hold on.
We were scolding Lada.
Why are we attacking each other?
Yeah, you're right.
Come on.
All right,
give me a reason
you pulled out of this commercial.
Because I didn't wanna be in a commercial with...
that presenter.
So what?
You usually don't hold grudges against anyone.
What was so bad that
you two can't work together?
Don't tell me...
Oh, my God.
Yes, Dad.
I was talking to the crew about today.
Why did you pull out suddenly?
I don't think I'm right for this job.
You're the hospital's owner.
Who would be more qualified?
He's right, Doctor.
You're right for it in every way.
You're beautiful and look expensive.
If you're not right, then no one else is.
I insist
that I really can't shoot this commercial.
Go ahead and replace me, Dad.
Then give me a reason why you're pulling out.
Because I don't want to be in a commercial with...
this presenter.
Can I ride with you?
I've just realized
that you became an irresponsible person.
What are you talking about?
You pulling out of this commercial I'm in.
Because you don't wanna be around me.
You're afraid you'd develop
feelings for me, aren't you?
Ridiculous.
If that's the case, why are you doing this?
Then prove it
that you're not into me anymore.
I'm sorry.
I don't need to prove anything
to someone like you.
When you're ready,
come back and work together, Doc.
♪ It may seem like I don't love you
That I'm okay ♪
♪ But the truth is, inside my heart ♪
♪ Every time I hurt you, I feel heartbroken ♪
♪ The pain is too much to describe ♪
♪ The more I see you sad, the more I break down ♪
♪ I try to erase the days
Erase the memories of when we were in love ♪
♪ But it just can't be done ♪
♪ I hate it but I still do it ♪
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape
But it feels like walking in circles ♪
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
♪ I try not to love you
Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
Mom!
Earn.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
How are you doing?
I prepared all your favorite dishes.
You see this shrimp?
I'm not hungry.
I just wanna hug you.
Eh?
What's wrong?
Hm?
Is there something wrong?
Is something bothering you?
Hm?
I ran into Doc today.
And she seemed to despise me.
We had to be in a commercial together,
but she pulled out because
she didn't want to work with me.
It's understandable.
Because you dumped her.
But I still don't understand even now.
You loved her so much.
Why did you dump her?
It was my fault
for not being firm enough.
It serves me right to have her hate me.
Remember when I was seriously sick?
Did you know
what I was afraid of the most?
I was afraid I wouldn't be
with the people I loved.
Like you and your father.
Life is unpredictable.
And love is not easy.
But it's not difficult.
If we already learned to love,
if we already knew love,
we have to love the right way
and learn to cherish that love.
But in the end, if it's not right for us,
we have to let it go.
No.
I won't let go of my love.
Okay.
It's all there.
It was hectic in the ER yesterday.
Hello.
I'm here to see Dr. Fahlada.
Earn.
-Hello.
-Did you make an appointment?
-I did.
You did. I'll contact her. Wait a second.
Oh, I want it to be a surprise.
Can you just tell me her room number?
And do you mind...
giving the doctor this food?
Uh...
Well...
Doctor, you have an OPD round in 10 minutes.
You've improved, Ms. Rose.
You prepared a surprise.
You found out I loved stir-fried glass noodles.
Uh...
It's not from me.
Then who?
It's from me.
Don't forget to eat.
Doctors can get sick too.
Ms. Rose.
Please leave us.
Sure.
Oh.
You're probably sick of stir-fried glass noodles.
I'll make you something else next time.
Don't.
Are you gonna leave willingly
or do I need to call security?
Fine.
I'll leave willingly.
But I'll be back.
I'll keep coming back until you give in to me.
I learned from my pain.
If you're in pain,
I'll get rid of that pain for you.
See you around.
Oops.
Please.
Yes.
What did you say?
Earn, Sanitada came to see Dr. Fahlada?
That's right. And more importantly,
she didn't come empty-handed.
She surprised Dr. Fahlada
with her favorite food on her desk.
-Oh, my God.
And what did Dr. Fahlada say?
I have no idea.
Dr. Fahlada kicked me out first.
Tan.
-Hm?
-I think
I smell disaster.
Right?
Lada went through hell to get here.
Why is this brat picking at old scabs?
Doctor?
Old scabs?
What do you mean?
Oh, don't you have an OPD round, Ms. Rossarin?
Oh, right!
I forgot. I was too busy gossiping.
I'm off, Doctors. Bye.
-Hey.
-Hm?
I'm starting to worry about Lada.
Me too.
What should we do?
Hey, girl.
Maybe we should find her a new girlfriend.
Because they say a good girlfriend
is a new girlfriend.
Yeah. If she has someone new,
she might get over this brat.
Get it done.
Does that hurt?
No.
You're very gentle.
Uh...
I mean...
It doesn't hurt but the skin burns.
Maybe I'm allergic.
I suspect you are.
Then I'll prescribe you a new medicine.
It's almost noon. Are you free?
Do you need something from me?
You've treated my skin for many years.
Can I treat you to a meal to repay you?
You're a patient and I'm a doctor.
Of course I treat you.
So that's a yes, right?
But usually at lunch
I only get a sandwich.
Uh, I don't think she'd get even a sandwich
because she has so many patients to see today.
Rain check?
But...
Uh, Doctor, are you done with Ms. Ratee?
Then if I may.
Ms. Ratee, you have so many fans
outside waiting to get your autograph.
Please.
Rain check it is.
Hello.
-Hello. Hello.
-Hello.
-Please sit here.
-Go sit down.
Thank you.
-Hello, ma'am.
Hello, Earn.
Whoa.
Engfah, hello.
You don't need to wai me.
I've always wanted to work with you.
I'm glad our schedules finally work out.
It's you I have to thank.
No wonder why you're this famous.
Everyone loves a nice girl like you.
She's right.
Sure.
Sorry.
Ratee, where are you?
A lot of people are waiting for you.
Jeez, I'm here. What's with the nagging?
I'm sorry. I've been having menstrual cramps.
I still do.
Oh, goodness me.
Goodness, goodness, Ratee.
Why didn't you call and tell me
you're having menstrual cramps?
Will you be able to shoot?
Of course I can. I won't trouble
other people because of my problem.
Oh!
What a spirit!
-Uh, Mr. Assistant Director?
-Yes?
Where should Ratee go for her makeup?
Uh...
Here is fine.
Is that a good idea, Engfah?
He's your regular makeup artist.
It's okay.
I finished a while ago.
Since...
I arrived on time.
No idea what I'm laughing about.
Earn reacts great.
Cut!
Okay, playback.
Let me check for a sec, girls!
Earn, here.
Are you okay?
Thank you, Engfah.
You're okay?
What's wrong?
Missing that brat?
How did you know?
Jeez.
If I didn't know, no one else would.
Look at yourself, Lada.
Even since you ran into that brat,
you've been moody.
Ms. Rose told me you made a mistake
in a medical certificate.
She did.
Ever since this morning
Dr. Fahlada seems very moody and irritable.
She's scolded me many times.
I hate feeling like this.
Do you want it to stop?
Bow, you know how?
Yes.
But you have to cooperate.
SATURDAY 30 MARCH
WISANU
Whoa.
Hey, is he a human or a ghost?
He's calling before I even mentioned him.
Answer, Lada.
Hurry, Lada.
Answer his call.
Come on, Lada.
Right now, Lada.
If you don't wanna talk to him,
want me to do it for you?
-Don't.
If you won't answer,
I'll do it myself.
WISANU
Here, come on.
Yes, Nu?
My company's working with
the Dermatological Society to held this talk.
You should come if you're available.
Let me check my schedule.
If I'm available, I'll be there.
Your mother told me you've been
working nonstop ever since you got back.
I believe her now.
I love my job.
I love seeing my patients get better.
Hearing that, I'm jealous of your patients.
They have such a lovely...
and caring doctor.
Yes.
Anyway, are you off work now?
Can I give you a lift?
I've been wanting to see your mother.
Uh...
I'm sorry, Nu.
Actually...
I made plans with a friend.
But if you wanna pay my mother a visit,
please feel free.
-Earn's great.
-Yes, beautiful.
-Ratee's great too.
-She's good too.
Earn really stands out.
Ratee's very outstanding.
Bang, bang.
Okay!
That's it for today!
-Good job.
-Ratee.
-See you!
-See you. Bye.
See you!
Ratee, are you tired?
You did great.
The director was praising you.
Really?
Oh, there's a party at Madam Ple's
house today. Wanna join me?
-Yes.
-I'd rather not, Engfah.
Not going again, Earn?
I actually have something to take care of.
What's that? You always have something.
Or you don't wanna come
because you don't like me?
No, Engfah. That's not it at all.
So that means...
you like me.
I'm kidding.
You're busy. I won't pester you.
Let's get together on our own.
We'll see each other a lot anyway.
Yes. So please excuse me, Engfah.
I'm off, Suzie.
-Eh?
-See you tomorrow.
Huh?
You're leaving me?
I have plans.
I should get changed.
Pu!
Eh? What's with her?
Jeez.
Doc? Doc.
Actually...
there's a new movie showing today.
and I don't have anyone to see it with.
Can you come with me as my friend?
Who's your friend?
I'm not your friend.
Oh? If not a friend,
can you come with me as my girlfriend?
That was just a joke.
No need to get angry.
Can't you talk to me nicely?
No.
Forget the movie. Let's go for a ride.
Forget the ride. Let's find
somewhere to enjoy music.
No.
Forget music. Let's go shopping.
Stop pestering me. It's annoying.
I just missed you.
I know you hate me.
Yes, I despise you.
Doc.
Doc, wait for me.
Doc, wait for me!
Doc!
Earn, watch out!
Why are you following me?
Just leave.
I still love you.
Love?
You dare use the word "love"?
I do.
I love you.
And I'll do everything to make you love me again.
There's no "again" between us.
Ms. Sanitada.
When you're stressed, look at this music box.
So you'll know you have me
by your side, always supporting you.
I wanna break up with you.
You're just a toy I've grown tired of.
Just let me go.
I don't like women! I like men!
I like men!
Do you get it now?!
I'm gonna make it happen.
I already told you
I'd do everything to make you love me again.
Here.
I'M SORRY. PLEASE, PLEASE.
I love you.
Do you love me?
Let's make up.
Who let a lunatic do something like this?
Go away.
Don't come near me.
Are you done, Ms. Earn?
I am.
I'll get someone to take these balloons away.
-Uh, Ms. Earn?
-Yes?
Can I take a picture with you?
Oh, of course.
-I'm... a fan.
-Thank you.
-Yes.
-Bear with me.
Of course.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
She's prettier in person.
May I sit with you, Doc?
Did you ask me if I wanna sit with you?
But I wanted to see your face.
At least for a bit.
Hey, wait up.
Ow.
So...
will you shoot the commercial with me?
It's okay if you don't answer.
Then are you free tonight?
After my shoot, I'll...
This will be my last warning.
Leave me alone.
You're so hard-hearted.
Watch out for heart diseases, Doc.
FBI My Love episode one,
scene 15, take one.
And... action!
This is a tricky situation.
We shouldn't trust those people.
I'll inform Lieutenant Chan.
We might get backup.
Lieutenant Chan? What can he do?
I think we should just raid their base.
Uh...
Let's go.
Cut! Cut! Cut!
Ratee missed her mark again.
Hey, didn't you brief her?
Uh, I kept telling her.
What should we do? Go again?
There's no time.
Let's get a different shot.
Eh?
That was take ten. Why did you write one?
Well...
One is a good number.
This way it looks like we haven't made mistakes.
What a day.
For the next shot,
move the camera to get her face.
Hey, Ratee.
Did you miss your mark?
You completely blocked Earn.
Oops.
I'm sorry.
I really didn't mean to.
I was so into it.
That's right, Mother.
Ratee acts from within.
Who's your mother?
Oops.
I feel sore.
Oh, you feel sore?
Let's go for a ride. Come on.
Try riding around.
Relax.
Wanna do another take, Earn? I'll tell Ek.
It's okay, Engfah.
Poor Ek. He's barely on schedule as it is.
How can he be?
Mistress Ratee needed a dozen takes.
Hey, Engfah invited you to join her workout.
I think it's a good idea.
I've been feeling bloated lately.
A little exercise will do me some good.
Up.
And down.
Suzie.
Are we going to exercise
or film the content for social media?
That's it.
You read my mind.
Anyway, where's Engfah?
There.
She's over there.
I'm so glad you can make it.
Then let's leave our car here
and get it back later?
Sharing a ride
helps reduce the world's pollution.
Uh...
I think Earn should ride with me
You can follow us in her car.
Uh...
That works too.
Oh.
Don't forget.
You have to let me post a video of
you two working out together.
You got it.
Let's go, Earn.
-Yes.
-Come on.
I smell something weird.
Since today Dr. Lada offered to treat us,
I'm gonna choose an omakase restaurant.
Fabulous. You've chosen very well, Dr. Bow.
You guys.
Let's get a full course today.
-I'm hungry.
-Go all out.
You got it.
Your shoes hurting your feet, Suzie?
Jeez.
Jealous, aren't you?
Who's jealous?
You like women, right?
Hello, Nu.
I was just thinking about you.
What if she gets so upset she hurt herself?
Did you think of that?
A woman was hit by a car in front of the hospital.
Stubborn girl.
You always worry me.
♪ Please don't let go of my hand ♪
♪ No matter what, please be right here ♪
♪ Having you here is reassuring ♪
♪ I'm less anxious than I used to be ♪
♪ You're the good love I never experienced ♪