(8 years ago)
Hey, baby girl!
Help! Help!
Hey, hey, hey.
-Where are you going?
Help!
-Don't hurt me. Don't hurt me.
-Come with me.
I'm begging you. Please let me go.
Hey!
Don't harass women again!
-Go!
-Let's go.
Come on.
Let's go.
Can you stand?
Are you hurt anywhere?
How will you get home?
My driver should be around here.
But my phone's dead.
Come on.
I'll help you find your car.
Cover yourself.
Your shirt is thin.
Oh! That's my car.
Thank you very much for saving me today.
My name's Ayla. What's yours?
Thank you.
Miss Jacket.
How is your owner so freaking cool?
She fought off three men.
With an umbrella like this.
How is she pretty, talented and cool?
Only one drawback.
She wouldn't tell me her name.
So how am I going to return this?
I'll probably never see her again.
So you'd better stay with me.
I'm talking to a jacket.
Hi, new kid. What's your name?
I'm Ayla.
And your first name?
Sasina.
And your last name?
Ruengkunakorn.
Hi, new friend. I'm Khaotu, Suthasinee Sawangkamol.
I've been here since Grade 7.
Nice to meet you, Ayla Sasina.
-Nice to meet...
-If you have questions, feel free to ask me
because I know everything
and everyone in this school.
But if grades stress you out,
you have nothing to worry about
because I...
get an A in every subject.
Okay, you're good.
Wanna hang out in the classroom or...
Hey!
Hey.
Khaotu.
(Don't leave this door open. Always close the door.)
Come on.
-So glad we got here in time.
-What's that?
Begin!
It's called kendo.
It's easy to follow. You score for every good hit.
You're awesome!
Wow!
-Wow!
-She's so good.
Resume play!
We've got a winner!
Hey, don't block.
-Sit down, sit down.
-Hey.
That senior.
She...
Her name is Tawan.
She's in Grade 12. An outstanding student.
The school president.
And she's our school's kendo champion.
She's a three-time champion.
Wow.
Good at school and sports?
She's good at everything.
And she's pretty.
Cool. The word is "cool."
Anyway, what club are you joining?
(Come Join the Kendo Club)
Are you really sure?
I am.
I want to join the kendo club.
But...
I think the training is very intense.
I don't think you can handle it.
I'm sure I can handle it.
I'm super ready. I'm all in.
Let's see how you do in a tryout.
Are you guys ready?
Yes!
By the look of it, that wimp won't make it.
Look at her. She's about to faint.
Let her join if she wanna join.
True.
And who's gonna train her?
I will.
You said it.
You train her.
Deal?
Deal.
All right.
Kid, no more running.
You're in.
Very good effort.
See you tomorrow at the club.
Get up and drink some water.
Hey, Tawan.
I feel lightheaded.
Are you okay?
Thank you, Tawan.
Do you remember me?
You know my name now.
This club is demanding.
Yes.
I'll try my best.
Thank you for accepting me.
Go.
Time to go home.
See you at the club tomorrow.
Ayla.
Bye-bye, Tawan!
She knows my name.
Ah!
Before we start,
I'll show you how we train kendo.
Fight! Begin!
Head! Begin!
Wrist! Begin!
Torso! Begin!
Bow!
You will start from the fundamentals.
Are you ready?
-Yes!
Kendo,
the way of the sword,
is based on the samurai swordsmanship.
To train the kendo fighting moves
that are fast, forceful and decisive,
deep concentration is required.
Come on.
Come on! Run!
Whoa!
Give us some.
Yeah, take some.
-Give me some.
-This one too.
Tawan got my gift.
She got my gift.
It's really pouring.
Tawan.
You haven't left?
Well, I forgot to bring my umbrella.
I forgot my umbrella too.
So...
why don't we find rain stoppers?
Rain stoppers?
What's that?
Let's make rain chasers.
Rain chasers?
Here.
Ooh, there's the sun. Very cool.
The sun is another word for "tawan."
Are you drawing the moon?
That's right.
Why the moon?
"Ayla" is another word for the moon.
I see.
The sun and the moon.
Tawan and Ayla.
♪ Never once did you notice ♪
♪ What my heart was feeling ♪
♪ When I look at you, my eyes say it all ♪
♪ Waiting only for you to pay me attention ♪
♪ My heart yells every day
But its voice never reaches you ♪
♪ I want you to know how long I've kept this in ♪
♪ Do you have any idea ♪
♪ As each minute goes by ♪
♪ How much my heart wants to say I love you? ♪
♪ All I know is my heart's stubborn ♪
♪ Even when you ignore me ♪
- ♪ There's pain but also love ♪
- Here we go.
♪ That has never lessened ♪
♪ The closer we are, the further it feels ♪
♪ Never once ♪
♪ Did you notice what ♪
♪ My heart was feeling ♪
♪ When I look at you ♪
- ♪ My eyes say it all ♪
- Look! The rain stops.
- ♪ Waiting only for you to pay me attention ♪
- It really works.
♪ My heart yells every day
But its voice never reaches you ♪
- ♪ I want you to know ♪
- Thank you, rain chasers.
♪ How long I've kept this in ♪
♪ Do you have any idea ♪
♪ As each minute goes by ♪
♪ How much my heart wants to say I love you? ♪
Tawan.
I'm good. Thank you.
-I'll take that.
-Tawan.
Hey.
You think you're so pretty, new kid?
You think Tawan accepts your drink
and you're better than everyone else?
You turn your nose up at everyone.
You want a drink?
Here.
I prepared it for you.
But not in a glass.
You'll get the whole bucket.
No. No. Don't do it!
Tawan.
Why did you have to go this far?
I'm sorry. It wasn't meant for you.
It was meant for this new kid.
She just got here.
How could she get this close to you?
I'm the reason, right?
I don't approve of this behavior.
Bullying is contemptible
and unacceptable.
No matter to whom.
It breaks my heart
that I'm not setting a good example.
Tawan, no.
It's not your fault.
You're very good. You've always been good.
It's our fault.
We're really sorry.
-I'm sorry.
Then let this end here.
I'm asking you.
Of course.
You ask, I obey.
We're good.
Huh?
We're good just like that?
Yeah.
Tawan asks, we obey.
Are you okay?
Thank you, Tawan.
For saving me.
You always protect me.
It's like you're my bodyguard.
Bodyguard?
I'm expensive.
Can you afford me?
Can I ask you something?
You love dancing, right?
Yes, I love dancing.
How did you know?
Well,
I saw you...
when you mopped the club floor.
You danced so hard
the floor was clean.
Huh?
Tawan got my gift.
You saw the whole thing?
I saw the whole thing.
I saw you were like...
I'm gonna cry.
You saw everything.
Our school has an excellent dance club.
I think you should join it.
Kendo is too much for you.
No, I like kendo.
I like kendo.
I even love it.
You love kendo...
more than you love dancing?
I think...
that's not true.
Why not?
Do I look that hopeless?
Yes.
Tawan, you're not very encouraging.
Just trust me.
Following your heart...
is always better.
But...
if I'm not in the kendo club,
I won't get to talk to you every day like this.
Of course you will.
You can say hi to me whenever you see me.
Or...
I train here every day.
You can come if you want.
It's a date.
♪ You are the moon in my heart ♪
♪ You make everything ♪
♪ More meaningful every day ♪
♪ I wanna be your sun ♪
♪ Please let me ♪
♪ Be by your side and keep on loving you ♪
♪ You bring light to the darkness ♪
♪ You make me smile every day ♪
♪ You make the lonely nights
More beautiful than they've ever been ♪
♪ Once looked lonely ♪
♪ They're now filled with your shadow ♪
♪ As the light to my heart ♪
♪ You are the moon in my heart ♪
♪ You make everything ♪
♪ More meaningful every day ♪
♪ I wanna be your sun ♪
♪ Please let me ♪
♪ Be by your side and keep on loving you ♪
♪ You are the moon in my heart ♪
♪ You make everything ♪
♪ More meaningful every day ♪
♪ I wanna be your sun ♪
♪ Please let me ♪
♪ Be by your side and keep on loving you ♪
I have something for you.
Hm?
What's that?
(Dance and Drama Club, audition for dancers
to compete in the annual contest)
You want me to compete?
Yes.
I want you to apply.
Think of it as a test of your ability.
But will I make it?
There are many seniors
who are good dancers in the club.
Come on.
Give it a try.
What's the harm?
Think of it as gaining experience.
All right.
I'll apply.
So on the day of the contest,
will you come and cheer for me?
I think that's doable.
Promise?
Promise.
Don't break your promise.
(Dance and Drama Club, audition)
Promise with a thumb stamp.
Ayla!
Tawan!
I thought you wouldn't make it.
I'm sorry for being late.
I got tied up with something.
It's okay. I'm just glad you made it.
I'm feeling so encouraged.
I couldn't possibly break my promise.
Hey.
What happened to your lips?
Just a small accident.
I'm okay.
Wait a sec.
I have some ointment on me.
Here.
You have it on you at all times?
I do. I must have it on me
at all times because I'm clumsy.
Here. I'll put it on you.
So you won't get a scar.
I'm done.
Here.
Keep it and apply it at home.
So you won't get a scar, okay?
Hello, Khaotu?
Oh, okay.
I'm coming.
Okay.
I have to go and prepare.
Please wait for my routine.
Ayla.
I want you to have it.
The school lapel pin?
But you haven't graduated.
Use it as a lucky charm.
Thank you.
Ayla!
(Thailand Passport)
I have a confession to make.
Thank you for always being there
and taking care of me.
The snacks I left in your locker
were my small thanks to you.
I'm so happy I attend the same school as you
and get to know you.
One last thing,
I love you.
I hope
it's mutual.
Why are you napping here, kid?
I came to see Tawan.
Where is she?
Hasn't she told you?
Told me what?
Well, she moved to another school.
Moved?
Do you have her address?
Who are you here for?
I'm here to see Tawan.
Is this her house?
Ms. Tawan doesn't live here anymore.
Then...
do you have her contact number?
I don't. I'm really sorry.
♪ I want you to know my heart for once ♪
♪ My gaze is me hoping for you to listen ♪
♪ To what my heart feels about you ♪
♪ But you never pay me any mind ♪
♪ No matter how much I try ♪
♪ You close your heart and keep ignoring me ♪
♪ The closer we are, the further it feels ♪
♪ Never once ♪
♪ Did you notice what my heart was feeling ♪
Now that you're by yourself,
the rain won't stop.
♪ When I look at you, my eyes say it all ♪
♪ Waiting only for you to pay me attention ♪
It's best you come home with me.
♪ My heart yells every day
But its voice never reaches you ♪
♪ I want you to know how long I've kept this in ♪
♪ Do you have any idea ♪
♪ As each minute goes by ♪
♪ How much my heart wants to say I love you? ♪
♪ All I know is my heart's stubborn ♪
♪ Even when you ignore me
There's pain but also love ♪
♪ That has never lessened ♪
♪ The closer we are, the further it feels ♪
♪ Never once ♪
♪ Did you notice ♪
♪ What my heart was feeling ♪
♪ When I look at you, my eyes say it all ♪
♪ Waiting only for you to pay me attention ♪
♪ My heart yells every day
But its voice never reaches you ♪
Can you promise me that
from this day on, no matter what happens,
you won't forget who you are?
Keep up your grades.
Follow your dreams.
I believe that your perseverance
will lead you down a good path.
Stay strong.
I'll always be rooting for you.
I promise you I will do my best.
I will realize my dreams.
Spotlights will shine on me.
And when I'm successful enough,
when every pair of eyes are fixed on me,
you will see me then,
and I will get you back.
Failed!
Go back to training.
I no longer trust your company.
I'll find my daughter's bodyguard myself.
As far as I know,
I don't meet your criteria at all.
I don't think we need to
look for another company, Dad.
Looking forward to working with you,
Ms. Bodyguard.
We have additional rules.
Always stay in
the bodyguard's line of sight.
How far is the line of sight?
Am I in your sight now?
♪ The closer we are, the further it feels ♪
♪ Never once ♪
♪ Did you notice ♪
♪ What my heart was feeling ♪
♪ When I look at you, my eyes say it all ♪
♪ Waiting only for you to pay me attention ♪
♪ My heart yells every day
But its voice never reaches you ♪
♪ I want you to know how long I've kept this in ♪
♪ Do you have any idea ♪
♪ As each minute goes by ♪
♪ How much my heart wants to say I love you? ♪
♪ When I look at you, my eyes say it all ♪
♪ Do you have any idea ♪
♪ As each minute goes by ♪
♪ How much my heart wants to say I love you? ♪