♪ You're the only one in my heart ♪
♪ Even if you never know ♪
♪ I'll keep watching over you ♪
♪ I love you more than words
but our path isn't easy ♪
♪ I just need you to believe in me ♪
♪ I'm weak for your lips ♪
♪ And the kiss upon my forehead ♪
♪ Every action conveys these words, you know? ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ Use the feeling you know ♪
♪ And you'll love so deeply ♪
♪ Can you feel my love? ♪
♪ Please know that I love you ♪
♪ In the moments when we look at each other ♪
♪ Even if I don't say it out loud ♪
♪ Deep inside, I only care about you ♪
♪ Love is so magical ♪
Don't say anything.
♪ And there aren't many sweet words ♪
Just listen to my heartbeat.
♪ Will always be you ♪
♪ I'm weak for your lips ♪
♪ And the kiss upon my forehead ♪
♪ Every action conveys these words, you know? ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ My love is in these soft whispers ♪
♪ You have to feel it with your heart ♪
♪ Our touches will make you understand ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ Use the feeling you know ♪
♪ And you'll love so deeply ♪
♪ Can you feel my love? ♪
♪ Please know that I love you ♪
Can I be the one setting the rhythm tonight?
Mm-hmm.
♪ You're the only one in my heart ♪
♪ Even if you never know ♪
♪ I'll keep watching over you ♪
♪ I love you more than words
but our path isn't easy ♪
♪ I just need you to believe in me ♪
♪ I'm weak for your lips ♪
♪ And the kiss upon my forehead ♪
♪ Every action conveys these words, you know? ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ My love is in these soft whispers ♪
MOM
Yes, Mom?
What?
You're at the gate?
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
What if I wasn't home?
So what? If you're not home,
I can leave the stuff with the maid.
Don't worry about me talking to your wife.
Not that I want to, anyway.
Mom…
So where is she?
It's a holiday. Neen's still sleeping.
If you hadn't come, I'd still be in the bed too.
Since when do you sleep in, huh?
Well… do you want to eat with us?
Thanks, but I already ate with your dad.
Do you want this now? I can heat it up.
It'll only take a minute.
-It's okay, Mom.
-Oh?
I can do it myself.
It's nothing, honey.
It's your day off. You should rest.
I'll take care of it.
If your wife won't take care of you, I will.
Neen works too, you know.
Besides, it's not her job to take care of me.
I don't expect her to do everything alone.
Works?
I doubt she works as hard as you do.
Has she ever done anything meaningful?
All she does is lounge around in pretty dresses.
Can you stop criticizing her like that?
Oh, Runch. You're blindly taking her side again.
Would it kill you
to admit you chose the wrong partner?
What's so wrong with me, Mother?
Your daughter loves me very much, you know.
Anyway…
what are you doing in my house this early?
Is that how you greet people?
And look at what you're wearing.
Like some pin-up girl.
Did you run out of decent clothes?
Is this how rich girls dress?
I'm not really into this style, Mother.
But Runch…
she says it's easy to take off. She likes it.
Ugh!
Shameless! Disgusting!
That's enough, Mom.
And you just woke up?
If I hadn't come, my daughter would've starved.
Oh, Mother. Your daughter can feed herself.
And she can feed me too.
Are you disabled or something?
Why does she have to do that for you?
I'm not disabled, you know.
But I'm Runch's little lovebug.
Oh my god!
You're just letting her do that?!
Oh, she lets me do a lot more than this.
She does everything I ask her to do.
Right?
You love taking orders from your wife, don't you?
Ah!
I can't take this anymore!
Enough, Mom! Just leave!
What?
You're kicking me out?
I'm not kicking you out, Mom.
But you should go.
Come on, I'll walk you out.
Let's go.
Come.
You're insane!
Mom!
Why are you--
-Ugh!
-Mom…
What are you doing? Why are you kicking me out?
Mom…
Enough, please.
This is exactly why I asked you
to let me know before coming over.
This is your house too.
Why do I need to let you know
or ask for your permission before I come?
Who told you it was mine?
Did you forget Neen's family
bought this house for both of us?
So that's why she's so arrogant.
Enough, Mom.
I don't want you coming here
because you're always like this.
Your wife started it.
No, Mom. Neen didn't start anything.
Runch!
Mom…
just go, okay? Please.
Come on.
Fine. But I'm only leaving
because you asked me to.
Neen…
go change and come downstairs to eat, okay?
I'm not eating.
You're not hungry?
Just leave me alone.
I own this house too, you know.
If you're bringing anyone over,
at least tell me first.
I don't want that babbling hag coming in here
and cursing at me.
This has been going on for way too long.
Neen!
She's my mother.
So what?
Am I supposed to just let her insult me?
Can't I insult her back?
Am I the only one
you're okay with getting insulted?
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry.
You know how my mom is.
She's hard to reason with.
So you're trying to put me in my place instead?
Aren't you tired of this?
You two are always fighting.
Of course I'm tired of it.
Honestly, I'm tired of you both.
But you know why she's like this?
Because you always let her do what she wants.
When she does something rude or wrong,
things no decent person would do,
that's when you should correct her.
And if you won't, then I will.
All this constant fighting is exhausting, okay?
I can't keep living like this.
She's the one who keeps insulting me!
Your mother's like a rabid dog,
and you still expect peace?
Neen!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
You're angry because I insulted her…
Were you ever angry when she treated me like that?
You're good at everything.
Everyone admires you.
You're good and successful at your job.
To everyone else, you seem so perfect.
But you know what?
As your wife and someone sharing a life with you,
I think you're the worst person!
I regret it.
I regret marrying you more than anything.
If I could go back in time, I'd never do it.
I'm sorry.
You said you wanted a divorce before.
Now I want one too.
But while we're still married,
just try to be a decent partner…
at least for this period,
as my family asked of you.
Pretend we still love each other.
Just once… make your mother choke
on how much we love each other.
Even if it's just for a short period of time
Neen…
Are you both sure about this divorce?
Yes.
We've both agreed on it.
I never thought I'd hear the two of you
say that so easily.
You're both adults…
and mature enough.
But… fine.
I trust you've thought this through.
I do have one request, though.
And it's very important.
For now, don't tell anyone about the divorce.
Not even your family, Runch.
I want this to stay within our family.
Iperis Group will open
its restaurants in four months.
There'll be press coverage, business partners…
This is a major event for our company and family.
And for the press release, we need the image
of a stable marriage.
Just four months…
Can you do that for me?
Yes.
Thank you.
This won't be easy.
But I promise you…
once these four months are over,
whatever decision you make,
I won't stand in your way.
Natee…
I think I really need to divorce Neen.
Huh?
Divorce?
Are you serious?
That's huge.
You two love each other so much. What happened?
Every time my mom and Neen see each other,
I have to watch the two people I love
hurt each other over and over again.
I want to protect both of them…
But in the end,
I can't do anything.
I can't protect either of them.
Neen's exhausted, you know.
Part of it is work…
but she's exhausted because of me and my mom too.
She keeps acting strong,
even though she's actually really sensitive.
Every time my mom insults her…
the look in her eyes…
It's like a hurt child with nowhere to go.
I love Neen so much, Natee.
So much that…
I don't think I'll ever love anyone else
the same way again.
But the more I love her…
the more I realize something.
I'm the reason
she's suffering like this. Because of my mom.
I didn't ask for a divorce
because I stopped loving Neen.
It's because…
I love her too much.
I love her enough…
to be the one who walks away.
So she won't keep getting hurt because of me.
You're back early, honey.
That woman… she made Runch kick me out.
You and Neen fought again?
I've told you so many times not to do this.
You're always like this.
And don't say I didn't warn you
when Runch finally snaps one day.
She's not the type to complain…
but once she reaches her limit, you'll regret it.
Runch has changed ever since she got married.
This is exactly why I was against their marriage.
I don't see anything wrong with Neen.
Not you too, Pong.
Why are you defending your daughter-in-law?
And stop with the empty threats.
Runch can be angry all she wants,
but I'm still her mother.
You're too sure about that.
Once people start their own family,
that family becomes their priority.
That's why I never wanted Runch to get married.
No. You just wanted her
to marry someone you liked.
At least I'd have peace of mind
if she married someone I actually got along with.
You've been picking at Neen
ever since they started dating,
just because you never approved of her.
And now that she's finally standing up
for herself,
you're making her out to be the villain.
Am I wrong about her, though?
Everything I said is true.
She's just some spoiled rich girl
who's dragging Runch down with her.
No decent woman
dresses that revealingly.
And her extravagant lifestyle and nightlife?
I can tell she's no good.
I don't care how rich she is.
She's not good enough for our daughter.
She's never brought anything good
into Runch's life. Ugh!
My mom invited us to dinner tonight.
Just the usual family gathering.
I can go alone if you don't want to come.
I never said I didn't want to go.
My parents would understand.
They already know we're getting divorced.
You don't have to pretend in front of them.
We're not divorced yet.
Can't I have dinner with my in-laws?
Whatever.
If you weren't so stubborn,
maybe she wouldn't have asked for a divorce.
Can you not rub it in right now?
Look, things would probably be better
if you softened up a little.
You both know what I've had to put up with,
and you still keep taking her side?
Her mom insults me nonstop.
She even drags my family into it.
And Runch never stands up for me.
Come on, she's stuck in the middle too.
So what?
My own family has never treated me like that.
They didn't raise me
just to get bullied by that hag, okay?
This is hard for me too!
Says the woman
who keeps calling her mother-in-law a hag.
Ex-mother-in-law, okay? Get it right.
Relax, you're not divorced yet.
We will be. Just wait.
Runch, try this.
I made it myself.
-Thank you, Mother.
-Of course.
You should have some too, honey.
-Thanks, Mom.
-Eat up.
Eat up, Runch.
You've gotten thinner lately, haven't you?
Yeah…
is everything okay?
Is your work too stressful?
You're not getting enough rest, right?
You can always tell me
if you're tired or need a break.
We're family too, okay?
Yes, Mother.
Runch…
no matter what happens…
you'll always be like a daughter to me.
I love you just as much as my own children.
Thank you.
Eat up.
-Here, try the sour curry.
-Today's a good day.
Let me pour my sister-in-law a drink.
Uh…
Okay.
But just a little, please.
Nai…
A strong woman like you
should be able to hold your liquor.
Just a little, okay?
Come on, don't be shy.
Nai, can you not do this right now?
It's okay.
Cheers.
Do it gently.
She's out after just two glasses?
You know Runch is a lightweight,
but you still did that to her.
Can you really blame me?
She had the nerve to bring up the divorce.
That's what she gets for breaking your heart.
Oh, grow up.
After everything…
you still care about her?
When you're finally divorced…
are you really going to be okay?
Think about it.
Why did you go over your limit, huh?
Well, Nai asked me to drink.
I didn't want to be rude.
You're way too polite.
Why are you smiling?
I'm just happy… that you're worried about me.
Don't kid yourself. I'm not worried.
I'm scolding you.
That still makes me happy.
It means you care.
You can go home first, Neen.
I'll call a driver.
Ah…
You're not calling anyone. We're going together.
-Oh?
-Come here.
Leave the car here.
I'll have my dad's driver
bring it to our place tomorrow.
You're the best, Neen.
Ugh…
You're in your room now.
Stop…
we're not like that anymore.
Why not?
I remember…
you used to like it.
Because now we're not…
We're not like that anymore.
Don't do this again.
Thank you.
Oh, come on…
What's wrong with your car?
It won't start. Battery's dead.
And I've got a meeting today.
In that case…
just get in my car.
I'll drive you.
I'm getting coffee. You want anything?
No.
What is there to talk about? It's just coffee.
Babe…
what's taking you so long?
Oh, there were a few people in line ahead of me.
Then why didn't you tell me?
I was bored waiting.
You should make it up to me, you know.
How?
You know… the usual.
Come on, babe.
Aww, you're so sweet.
My darling is the best.
Ms. Runch, your drink is ready.
-Thank you.
-Oh.
Thank you very much.
Let's go, babe.
Did you just get jealous?
I wasn't jealous.
I was just annoyed.
You seem pretty familiar with them…
You must come here a lot.
I do. I come here every day.
Tch. Now I'm wondering
if you're really here for coffee.
I'm here for coffee, of course.
There are so many other coffee shops.
Why does it have to be this one?
Look…
You really don't remember?
This is our special place.
Thanks for the ride.
Let me help you carry your things.
You brought a lot.
No need.
I'll help.
Just let me.
Hello, Ms. Neen.
Hello.
-Hello, Ms. Runch.
-Hello.
Well, it's been a while since I last saw you.
Oh…
I've just been busy with work lately.
I see.
That's good to hear. I was worried
you two might have had a fight.
You know, I really look up to you both.
Everyone here sees you
as the ideal couple.
I'll have your car fixed for you.
I'll pick you up this evening.
No need.
I can get my own ride.
That won't do.
Don't forget… we're everyone's ideal couple.
We can't disappoint them.
See you this evening, okay?
I'm telling you,
if Runch hadn't married the owner's granddaughter,
there's no way she'd be our boss.
Exactly.
She makes mistakes sometimes,
but no one dares say anything.
What kind of boss dumps work
on her team like that?
And she never says anything in meetings.
Just sits there like a prop to make the company
look more progressive.
I wonder…
is she actually capable, or is it just because
her partner is the Iperis heir?
Who knows.
But if I were her, I'd feel pretty insecure.
Even after marrying into the owner's family,
she's still just a figurehead.
Nobody really respects her.
Yeah. When she walks by,
everyone just goes quiet and works.
No one really talks to her.
She probably doesn't get along with anyone.
Maybe she knows
she's not that capable,
so she just keeps to herself.
Hiding it, you know?
Oh… Boss.
Coffee?
They said it's the electrical system.
It'll take a few days to fix.
I'll drive you for now.
You don't have to.
I'll ask my dad for a spare car.
No need to trouble yourself.
It's not trouble if it's for you.
This isn't the way home.
Let's eat first. Then we'll go home.
I ordered your favorite.
Eat up, okay?
Why are you doing this?
What do you mean?
No one here knows us.
So why are you being nice to me?
I just want to do things for you like I used to.
Like before? When nothing is the same anymore?
What do you want from me?
Are you trying to mess with my feelings?
That's not what I'm doing.
I just want us to separate on good terms.
There's no need.
You already ruined every good memory I had
the moment you brought up divorce.
So stop being nice to me.
Stop acting like you still know me.
I don't want to get used to you
being by my side again.
You probably don't want to see me,
so I've headed to work.
Don't forget to eat this, okay?
From Runch.
You really know me so well…
♪ In the moments when we look at each other ♪
♪ Even if I don't say it out loud ♪
♪ Deep inside, I only care about you ♪
♪ Love is so magical ♪
♪ Even though sometimes I don't treat you right ♪
♪ And there aren't many sweet words ♪
♪ But I want you to know that ♪
♪ My life partner will always be you ♪
♪ I'm weak for your lips ♪
♪ And the kiss upon my forehead ♪
♪ Every action conveys these words, you know? ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ My love is in these soft whispers ♪
♪ You have to feel it with your heart ♪
♪ Our touches will make you understand ♪
♪ Can you hear me saying I love you? ♪
♪ Use the feeling you know ♪
♪ And you'll love so deeply ♪
♪ Can you feel my love? ♪
That's the one.
I have it in blue, but not in pink yet.
-Then you have to get it.
-Yeah.
-It's gorgeous.
-And it's 10% off too.
-Look at that one.
-Oh, that's pretty.
Right?
-Should we go take a look?
-Oh? Isn't that Neen?
Yeah.
Ging, isn't that your beautiful daughter-in-law?
Probably not.
-No, that's definitely her.
-Hello!
Hi, Neen!
Hello, everyone.
-Hello.
So nice to see you.
You've gotten even prettier.
Thank you.
Oh, Neen,
Ging was saying she wanted this designer scarf.
She really likes it, but it's expensive.
-That's 35,000 baht.
-Hey…
Do you think you could get it for her?
Of course.
You really don't have to.
I want to, Mother.
You're Runch's mother.
Of course I should treat you well.
Please don't hold back.
You're so kind, Neen.
That's your perfect daughter-in-law.
Right?
-Isn't she just the sweetest?
-Yeah.
Here you go, Mother.
Don't worry, I'm happy to buy it for you.
Oh, and one more thing…
Since everyone's here,
I got something for both of you too.
Oh no, dear, we couldn't possibly…
Please, you have to accept them.
-Wow…
-Thank you so much, Neen.
I'll treasure this.
Are you all going somewhere after this?
We're having lunch together.
Lunch?
Mother,
please take this.
Treat yourself and your friends to something nice.
Please order whatever you like.
It's my treat. Don't hold back.
I have somewhere else to be,
so I'll excuse myself now.
Goodbye.
-Goodbye, dear.
-Goodbye.
You're so lucky to have Neen as a daughter-in-law.
Yeah.
I've always wanted this one.
-Oh, Mom--
-Peeracha!
Come out here!
Get out here right now!
What's going on, Mom?
Ask your sneaky little wife what she did!
You humiliated me in front of my friends.
Made me look like I'm living off your money!
What did I do wrong?
I was just helping an old woman
so she wouldn't starve to death.
Mom, please. Let's talk outside.
Stay out of this!
-Mom! Come with me!
-Runch!
Did you just raise your voice at me?!
Has she already turned you against me?!
Ugh, you're such a nuisance!
Mom!
Neen…
Mom…
come with me.
Now.
Runch…
Runch, I didn't mean it…
THREE YEARS AGO
That's a pretty big stain.
Maybe you should change your shirt.
It's okay.
I'm almost off work anyway.
And I don't have a spare.
A wet shirt can be kind of revealing, you know?
If you don't mind, you can borrow mine.
I haven't worn it yet.
I don't want to trouble you.
It's fine.
Please take it.
Walking around in a wet shirt feels awful.
I'll go grab it from my car.
Thank you.
I'll wash it and return it to you soon.
May I…
have your email?
My email?
Wouldn't a phone number be easier?
Here.
Done. I'm Neen. And you are?
Runch.
Do you work around here?
Somewhere nearby.
Nice to meet you, Runch.
She thinks having connections and a rich wife
makes her untouchable?
Be a man.
There are plenty of ways
to make people think we're in love.
Let's do all of them.
You know Neen hates me.
And I know you hate her too.
-Come here.
-Huh?
-Ugh!
-Stop it…
♪ Living with pain and love ♪
♪ Living while waiting and losing hope ♪
♪ A voice inside my heart says enough ♪
♪ But another voice asks me to endure ♪
♪ I stay because I love you, you know? ♪
♪ I still believe in the love between us ♪
♪ Please let us go back to how we were ♪
♪ I don't know if our love is just impossible ♪
♪ Or if there's a reason for all of this ♪
♪ And that reason is you don't love me ♪