♪ I have a heart and know how to love ♪
♪ Especially when I see you
I keep seeing the scenes ♪
♪ From when we were together ♪
♪ But I keep seeing you in my head ♪
♪ My broken heart hasn't recovered ♪
♪ So I hurt you ♪
♪ Even though I have to
Make myself watch you cry ♪
♪ I hate it but I still do it ♪
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape
But it feels like walking in circles ♪
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
♪ I try not to love you
Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
Missing that brat?
Even since you ran into that brat,
you've been moody.
I hate feeling like this.
Do you want it to stop?
You know how?
Yes, but you have to cooperate.
-I know you hate me.
-Yes, I despise you.
Earn, watch out!
I still love you.
Love? You dare use the word "love"?
I do. I love you.
And I'll do everything
to make you love me again.
There's no "again" between us.
YOU'LL LIKE IT
Hey, this one's delicious.
You're right.
Lada.
Here. Enjoying the food?
She's not enjoying it.
Jealous, aren't you?
That's why you're taking it out on your friends.
Who's jealous?
Duh. Aren't you aware at all?
Even since you saw your ex
walking with that actress,
you've been so obvious.
You're wrong.
Fine. Whatever you say.
You can lie to us all you want.
but you can't lie to yourself.
Because you're being super obvious.
Hey, come on.
You don't have to say everything you know.
Lada's well aware.
I'm not bothered.
It's her business who she hangs out with.
Why would it bother me?
Okay, okay, okay.
So you're not bothered.
I'm the only bothered one here.
Look at us. We finally found the time
to hang out outside the hospital,
I didn't get my free omakase.
Hey, this is free too.
Because Lada's treating us.
Oh, then let's eat.
I'm happy now.
Come to mama.
This looks so good.
Enjoy this free food. I'm enjoying it.
Please do.
You're drenched.
Huh?
This is so cute.
Thank you, Engfah.
I'll do it myself.
Sure.
-Engfah?
-Hm?
Can I ask you something honestly?
What's up? Why are you being so serious?
Let me ask you honestly.
You like women, right?
Why are you asking me that?
I'm just curious.
Yes.
I like women.
Got it.
Hold on.
I'm not finished.
Yes?
If you're the woman I'm into,
what would you say?
Lada. You're okay.
You're okay.
You're okay, I'm okay, me okay, okay?
Okay.
Doctor, your first patient's here.
Please let them in.
Hello, Doc.
Not okay.
What did you say?
Please leave, Ms. Rose.
I'll take care of this one myself.
I see.
Got it, Doctor.
I got you banoffee pies.
Dang, I can't hear anything.
I have to get Doctors Bow and Tan.
You don't like banoffee pies anymore?
I stopped liking it two years ago.
Please leave.
I know you don't want to see me.
But I still want to see you every day.
That's your problem.
And my problem is to figure out
how to get you out of my life.
No, I won't get out...
I have someone I love now.
And I'm going to marry him soon.
The person you're talking about...
Is he Dr. Wisanu?
How did you know?
I happened to watch TV the other day.
And I saw his interview.
But from what I heard...
you're not into him.
He's still trying to win you.
Do I need to kiss him...
for you to believe me?
Do it.
I want to know too
if you can kiss a man.
WISANU
I think you'll get more than a kiss.
Hello, Nu.
I was just thinking about you.
What's that?
You're coming to see me?
Of course you can.
Hurry.
I missed you.
PLASTIC AND SURGERY DEPARTMENT
Hello, Nu.
Oh, just now?
No, I didn't say that.
You probably heard it wrong.
I said...
I missed Taohu.
I want to play with him.
Okay.
Yes.
Dr. Fahlada, you have
a 001 case on the second floor.
I repeat. Dr. Fahlada,
you have a 001 case on the second floor.
Nu, I have an urgent case.
I don't think I can see you today.
I have to go.
Lada,
did you go overboard?
She looked like she was crying.
You're exaggerating.
She wasn't crying. She just got teary eyes.
Emotional pain can't be
measured by the amount of tear.
I could tell from just her face
that she was in great pain.
That was nothing compared to
what she did to me.
That's right.
You weren't there when that brat hurt Lada.
You wouldn't get it.
Fine.
I don't know.
We're all women.
I can't help empathizing with her.
It can't be helped.
She chose to come to me.
Hey, Lada.
Are you wavering?
No.
Good. That's my girl.
What if she gets so upset she hurt herself?
Did you think of that?
No way.
She's too self-absorbed to ever hurt herself.
She would only hurt other people.
Trust me.
-But I...
-Jeez, Bow.
Whose friend are you?
Why are you making her doubt?
She was about to get past it.
Fine.
I was asking just in case.
But if you two are sure, then never mind.
I hope she'll get over it soon.
Dr. Bow, the ER called to get you.
I sneaked out just for a bit.
A woman was hit by a car
in front of the hospital.
Really?
Where are you going, Doctor?
Come on.
Where's the patient who got hit by a car?
Oh, this way, Doctor.
Earn?
Uh...
I'll dress your wounds.
Where are you hurt?
Dr. Fahlada?
I'm an ER doctor.
You forgot I studied
emergency medicine, didn't you?
Yeah.
Please.
Dermatology's that way.
-What are your symptoms?
-That's right.
I'm going to have to press it.
If anything hurts, let me know.
You were worried about her
but lied that you weren't.
You're an awful liar, Lada.
No.
I wasn't worried about her.
I was worried about
the patient who got hit by a car.
-Really?
I wouldn't believe you
even if you were the Buddha.
I assure you
that person died to me a long time ago.
What if...
she came back to life?
How can dead people come back to life?
-Ooh.
-Harsh.
Hey!
Miss? Miss, are you all right?
Someone just went into shock in the ER.
This is a hospital.
People go into shock almost every day.
What's so exciting?
But this was Earn, the actress.
She came to our ward this morning.
-Really?
-Yes.
Doctor.
Ple just told me someone
went into shock in the ER.
Leave other wards alone.
Is my patient here yet?
I don't want to meddle, Doctor.
But this person is Earn, Sanitada.
Please relax. The doctor's coming.
Breathe slowly.
-What are the vital signs?
-BP is 90/50.
Pulse rate is 100 per minute.
SAT is 95 percent.
Give her Ventolin
and free-flow normal saline.
The patient has a banana anaphylaxis, Doctor.
I suspect the same thing here.
Are you related to the patient, Doctor?
Yes.
Uh, I saw she was eating a banana.
It's probably like what Dr. Lada said.
Then give her adrenaline at 1/1000.
0.5 ml IM.
CPM 1 amp IV. Dexa 5 mg IV. And...
Doc?
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
I'm so glad
you're the first person I woke up to.
Is this a happy matter?
You did something stupid.
Did you have a death wish?
Doc, you're misunderstanding me.
How's that?
You ate a banana
when you knew you were allergic.
What was that if not a death wish?
I just wanted to know...
if you would care about me.
If that's the case, you're being selfish.
Didn't you realize
the ER was for urgent care?
There were sick people
who needed nurses and doctors.
But you hurt yourself
to get attention?
Learn to think of other people.
Don't just think about yourself.
You're right.
I'm being selfish.
But I did it because
I was afraid I'd lose you to...
To Dr. Wisanu.
Listen to me, Earn.
You lost me a long time ago.
♪ My broken heart hasn't recovered ♪
♪ So I hurt you ♪
♪ Even though I have to
Make myself watch you cry ♪
♪ I hate it but I still do it ♪
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape
But it feels like walking in circles ♪
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
I don't like women! I like men!
I like man!
Do you get it now?
Earn!
Earn! Earn! Earn! Don't leave!
♪ Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
She's gone. She left me.
You're just a toy I've grown tired of.
Just let me go.
Please don't leave me, Tan.
I've been fooling you.
Because I knew you were rich.
I just wanted a comfortable life.
From this day on,
let's not see each other again.
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
Lada, calm down.
Calm down.
Breathe.
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
Something wrong, Doctor?
No.
Do you need something?
Your patient's here.
Please let them in.
Okay.
Suzie.
Here, take them.
You having difficulty sleeping
is the only reason
I drove back to get your old plushies.
-Thank you.
-Enough!
Leave your thanks there.
Don't you dare thank me.
Because I'm so mad at you.
Why?
You're allergic to banana
and you still ate it.
Look at yourself.
What if you don't recover
in time for the shoot?
You knew you had responsibilities.
A hundred of crew members
work to support their families.
You're wasting their time
because you hurt yourself.
Is that right?
I'm sorry.
Jeez.
I'm glad you've learned your lesson.
If you do this again, I won't talk to you.
Remember that.
Jeez.
All right, I'll stop scolding you.
All right.
Jeez.
I'll stop scolding you.
Your eyes will get puffy
and we'll have to fix them.
You're right for being angry.
What a stupid thing to do for an adult.
She was lucky to be alive.
I think she ran out of ideas to win you back
so she made that choice.
She knew I'd never go back to her.
She should've left me alone.
Instead, she kept pestering me.
It's annoying.
Let's just eat.
Here, have some orange.
Orange. Not banana.
Hey.
How long are you going to make a sour face?
It's upsetting seeing you like this.
What are they talking about?
I never wanted to get involved,
but as Lada's close friend,
I really can't let this go.
Can you do me a favor?
Will you leave my friend alone?
Doc asked you to tell me, didn't she?
No, she didn't.
But I feel for her.
You've hurt her enough.
But I didn't mean to.
I was hurt too.
But not as much as she was.
Have you any idea the day you left her,
her life was a living hell?
She walled off everything.
She abandoned everything.
Her future.
Her education.
Even her family.
My friend's life was ruined once.
Please don't ruin it again.
Doc...
was really that hurt?
Yes.
She was hurt in the way you couldn't imagine,
Ms. Earn.
Hello, girl.
Come on,
I'm planning on shopping before class.
Lada?
Why are you crying?
Tan.
What's wrong?
Earn left me.
Huh?
Why?
She's gone. She left me.
Calm down. Calm down.
-It's because I'm not a man, isn't it?
-Calm down, Lada.
-So she left me.
-Lada.
-Why...
Lada, calm down. Calm down.
Lada.
Here, take it.
What's that?
Lecture notes.
I went to your classes for you.
At this rate, I'll be a dermatologist
instead of a surgeon.
Great.
Lada, when will you stop acting like this?
This is so not you.
What am I usually like?
More human than this.
I'm still a human.
A good human too.
Enough, stop drinking, Lada.
Let go.
Stop drinking.
-Give it!
-No!
-Lada, you've been drinking... No!
-Give it!
Lada, stop!
-You won't give it back?
-Stop!
Stop! Lada, enough. Enough. That's enough.
-Give it to me.
-Give it back!
-You want it?
-Tan...
Jeez. You're drunk every day.
This won't do.
You stink.
-Stink of what?
-Stink of booze. What else?
I disgust you?
Oh!
Oh! Lada!
Jeez.
Come here.
Don't breathe on me. It stinks.
Hey, hey, hey!
Lada, are you going to barf?
Enough, girl.
That's enough.
Let go, Lada.
Here.
Lecture notes.
I go to so many of your classes
I'm about to graduate with you.
Lada.
When will you get back up?
You can't let yourself go like this.
Stop crying and...
Will you please stop crying?
Lada cried to me...
over you all the time
because she didn't know
the real reason you left.
I love her.
Why are you hurting my friend again?
Her life was getting better.
Please let my friend go.
What you're doing right now...
is like you're hurting
a patient who's almost healed.
Let me remind you.
If a patient who's almost healed...
gets seriously hurt again,
they might succumb to their wounds...
and end up dead for real.
But I didn't mean to.
I did what I did because...
The reason doesn't matter anymore.
I see what you're doing.
The way you're harassing her,
it makes her uncomfortable.
Lada's been kind to you
for not hurting you more.
Because if I were her,
you would've never stepped inside this hospital.
Stubborn girl.
You always worry me.
Doctor?
Dr. Fahlada?
Wrong room.
What's with her?
You lost me a long time ago.
Will you leave my friend alone?
Have you any idea the day you left her,
her life was a living hell?
Her life was getting better.
Please let my friend go.
What if I ask you for one last chance?
I promise it won't end like last time.
This time I'm going to make her
a completely healed patient.
I'm going to heal her heart myself.
New skirt. Isn't it pretty?
Watch me.
What's this, Suzie? Let me see.
It's fabulous, auntie.
-Pack up.
-Fold it.
How are you feeling, sick girl?
Engfah?
How did you get here?
Suzie texted me via LINE last night
that you were sick and admitted here.
So I came by to visit.
I'm fine now.
I was released me this morning.
I'm glad I made it in time
or I would've found someone else here.
You're so sweet, Eng,
for taking your precious time to visit Earn.
So let's leave, shall we?
I need sleep.
-Let's go.
-Give them here.
-Huh?
-I'll carry them.
-Everything?
-Yes.
Come on.
I'll help you with this one.
Come on, I'll help.
-Thank you.
-Let's go.
-Can you manage?
-Yes, piece of cake.
Oh!
Dr. Fahlada, hello.
Hello.
You're leaving?
Yes. Oh, thank you so much
for arranging the room for Earn
before I got here
The staff arranged it.
I didn't do anything.
Doc.
I...
I'm leaving.
Goodbye.
I've heard a lot about you.
I'm glad to finally meet you.
Well, it'd be inappropriate
to say I hope to see you again.
Since the reason we see a doctor
is that we're sick, right?
We can meet for other reasons.
There won't be one.
Who's calling?
Is it a scammer?
Hello?
Oh!
A duo gig?
Wow.
I'll call you right back.
How has this video gotten so many views?
-What video?
-Duh.
The video of you two of course.
I thought it was cute so I posted it on IG.
It got so much attention.
This is so cute.
Ooh, just a sec.
-Oh!
-Huh?
"Earn's Eng."
A new fandom.
By the look of it,
The two of you, Eng and Earn,
will become a new imagined couple.
Let me take this call.
-Hello?
-Today we're an imagined couple,
but in the future,
we might become a real couple.
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
Hello, Engfah, where are you?
What mood are you in, Doctor,
that got you sit alone quietly here?
When Earn arrives,
maybe she should sit here?
Eh? Where are you going?
A different bar.
Goodness, she's wasted.
-Plus she's alone.
-Suzie?
I'll take care of her.
Doc, why did you get so drunk?
♪ Please don't let go of my hand ♪
♪ No matter what, please be right here ♪
♪ Having you here is reassuring ♪
♪ I'm less anxious than I used to be ♪
♪ You're the good love I never experienced ♪