♪ I have a heart and know how to love ♪
♪ Especially when I see you
I keep seeing the scenes ♪
♪ From when we were together ♪
♪ But I keep seeing you in my head ♪
♪ My broken heart hasn't recovered ♪
♪ So I hurt you ♪
♪ Even though I have to
Make myself watch you cry ♪
♪ I hate it but I still do it ♪
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape
But it feels like walking in circles ♪
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
♪ I try not to love you
Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
Attention please. Code 000 at the ER.
Where's my daughter?
Can you speak English?
I want to go find my daughter. Where's my daughter?
-Can anyone here speak Chinese?
-No, Doctor.
Could you please speak English?
I want to go find my daughter.
Calm down please. I'll ask them for you.
She came in with her daughter.
Do you know where she is?
She's in Bed 3. Dr. Pannaorn is with her.
Your daughter is already in the care of the doctors.
Don't worry. We will do our best.
Okay. Please help her.
Please save my daughter.
In this case I suspect an inhalation burn
and a second-degree burn of about
5% on her right limbs.
I'll leave you to it. I have another case to tend to.
Sure.
The patient has an inhalation burn.
Her blood pressure is dropping.
Prepare intubation and start a central line.
Yes, Doctor.
Look at you guys.
You look like you've just fought a war?
Trauma patients came in droves.
Thankfully Lada helped me
or else I would've been screwed.
Hey,
since you're great at everything,
study emergency medicine
and come work with me.
Very funny.
What about my dermatology ward?
Just work in both wards.
Bow.
Just because she's the owner's daughter,
you expect her to work in two wards?
She's gonna die as it is.
Don't die yet.
Refresh with coffee first.
And go back to work.
-You're the devil.
Not so fast.
I'm a nurse.
A nurse.
Yes.
Ah, just now
the staff in the ER were talking
how Dr. Lada was such a badass
for talking to a Chinese patient
without using an interpreter.
Of course.
She was an exchange student.
Speaks almost every language.
Except...
love language, right?
That's why Dr. Lada's still single.
Ms. Rose?
When am I scheduled to do my round today?
Uh...
You're not.
You have to shoot a commercial today.
Dr. Fahlada, please wait a moment.
The presenter is coming.
Sure.
The presenter is here!
Oh, hello there!
I missed you, Doc.
I'm sorry.
-I'm so sorry.
-It's okay.
Your way.
How can someone be that pretty?
Thank you.
You're Thai?
Yes.
I'm Thai.
Your coffee.
Thank you.
I'm so glad to meet a Thai person here.
Ever since I got here,
I haven't met Thai people.
It's been so lonely.
Always felt I was by myself.
What do you study here?
I'm studying management. What about you?
I'm studying medicine.
Wow, you're a doctor too?
-What's so excited about that?
-Duh.
I haven't met a doctor this beautiful.
You say that like you're not beautiful.
You're the first person to say I'm beautiful.
People usually say I'm...
childish.
So...
if I call you...
"Doc,"
will that be okay?
I think it's cool.
As you wish.
Call me whatever you want.
And if I'm into you,
what should I do?
Do nothing.
Go back to work first.
Sorry.
Okay.
Hi.
What would you like to order?
Can I get...
Chocolate cake.
Okay, what else?
Can I get...
hot milk?
Two please.
-Thank you.
-Just a moment please.
Thank you.
Let's take a photo.
Come on.
Get more at the top.
Huh?
Hm?
Kiss.
Here's your order.
Thank you.
It looks so yummy.
Okay, just a moment please.
Again. One more.
I love seeing something like that.
It's a feast for the eyes.
Doc?
Have you eaten?
I got this for you in case you're hungry.
I'll leave it here.
Bye-bye.
She's a menace.
DON'T FORGET TO EAT.
DOCTORS CAN GET SICK TOO.
Here's your coffee.
Hey!
How much?
What do you mean "How much?"
I'm not the kind of person you're looking for.
-Calm down.
-What...
What happened?
-Nothing.
-He touched me
and he asked me how much.
You have any proof?
I know that all Asian girls
are lying and ask about money.
Bitch.
Hey, watch your language.
Did you forget we have CCTV cameras here?
Over there and there.
If you have problem with Asian girls,
you can contact my lawyer.
I've changed jobs many times.
And I've always been insulted and bullied.
But I never gave in so I punched back.
Hey.
You assault other people.
Aren't you afraid of getting sued?
I would run.
I'd run like hell and disappear.
So let me ask you honestly.
Why do you have to work this hard?
Are you putting yourself through school?
No.
My parents pay for it.
But I wanted to lighten their burden.
The cost of living here is high.
So...
if there's anything I can do, let me know.
Can you take me in and support me?
Think of it as helping an innocent kid.
I'm kidding.
Earn?
Why are you sleeping here?
Well,
my roommate's boyfriend came by
so I...
came down to read.
Are you sick?
A little headache.
I don't think it's little.
You're burning up.
Why don't you come to my apartment?
Did you know Son-in-law eggs were my favorite?
What's your favorite?
You.
Earn! Come eat.
Son-in-law eggs.
Ow.
Stop.
Yours is rice soup.
So you can take your med.
Jeez.
Did you know Son-in-law eggs were my favorite?
My all-time favorite.
But I haven't had them since I got here.
What's your favorite?
You.
Stir-fried glass noodles.
I see, stir-fried glass noodles.
If so, I'll learn to cook
mean stir-fried glass noodles
and make it for you every day, okay?
Then I'm gonna learn to cook
mean Son-in-law eggs for you too.
Maybe I get to be the daughter-in-law.
Huh?
-Hello.
These flowers are for you.
Thank you.
Valentine's Day.
Can you sign for me here please?
Someone must have sent her flowers.
-Okay.
-Thank you. Have a nice day.
Thank you. Have a nice day.
They're pretty.
You like them?
They're just pretty.
They're for you.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Doc!
They're for me?
Please date me,
my stubborn girl.
I will.
Hello,
my love.
Hello, my heart.
MY HEART
You're adorable.
Focus on your study.
I love only you.
I'm back.
Oh, you're back?
Look. This is my dream house.
It's my dream that one day I will own this house.
It must be expensive.
It is, but...
if I work and start saving up now,
I should be able to afford it when I'm 40.
Or 50.
Sixty.
Seventy.
Eighty.
I can't wait until eighty. I'll be too old.
I'd rather lying around with my dog and you.
Eighty for real?
Here.
A jigsaw puzzle?
That's right.
What's the picture? Can you show it to me?
Secret.
Secret?
When you're done,
you'll find out this picture is very important
to our relationship.
Really?
Mm-hm.
Thank you.
FAHLADA & EARN
Don't open your eyes.
Am I gonna crash?
-You won't.
-Am I gonna crash?
You won't.
-Close your eyes.
-They're closed. I won't look. Promise.
Sorry.
Come on. I'll let you see.
I'm so excited!
One,
two,
three!
Happy birthday to my love!
You made everything yourself?
No, I hired someone.
I'm joking.
Of course I made it myself.
Do you like it?
I do. Thank you.
-Here.
-What did you make?
I made this.
A banoffee pie.
This is my first time making it.
I'll feed you.
Here.
I'll give you a big bite.
Ah...
You don't like it?
I put a lot of effort into this.
Of course I like it.
It's made by my girlfriend.
Here you go.
Well? Is it good?
You like it, don't you?
Ah...
Is it good?
Earn?
What's wrong?
Earn? Earn?
Earn?
Breathe.
It's okay.
Earn, are you okay?
Doc?
You can't take it off.
But it's uncomfortable.
You can't.
Earn.
It was uncomfortable.
You're so stubborn.
Why didn't you tell me
you were allergic to bananas?
I didn't want to offend you.
You put a lot of effort into it.
I just wanted to surprise you on your birthday.
But it's ruined now.
Really?
Says who?
Doc!
Let me?
You're not allergic to anything here?
Doc.
You're ruining the moment.
Make a wish first.
Doc.
Wait a sec. This shawl.
Let me put this down.
-Do you like it?
-I do.
I had it custom-made.
To represent us.
F.E.
Fahlada.
Earn.
You like it?
I do.
I'll put it on you then.
Come on.
What should we have for dinner, Doc?
Anything is fine. Whatever you want, Earn.
So...
how about Chinese?
Or maybe we should get sushi?
At your favorite restaurant.
But I want Son-in-law eggs.
Maybe we should make them?
Let me study a little.
I get you have to study
but your non-answers don't tell me
if I have to dress up for dinner...
Doc.
That's your punishment for not letting me study.
If that's my punishment,
I'm happy to talk all day long.
Stubborn girl.
Oh, you're not studying anymore?
I can't concentrate.
Look at this.
Who are they?
Lada, of course.
Our daughter is turning into a perv...
A homosexual.
So what?
What do you mean, "So what?"
What do you mean by that?
Lada is a daughter of a hospital's owners.
She's going to be a doctor.
She'll take over our hospital one day.
She's currently dating a woman.
It's her happiness.
But I can't accept it.
You're not bothered by this at all, are you?
I'm her father.
I'm not her owner.
And sexual orientation is personal.
We shouldn't intervene.
Okay.
That's it then.
Let's agree to disagree.
If you're gonna be indifferent,
it's your business.
But I won't allow it.
Lada must break up with that girl
and marry only the person I choose.
Come in.
Lady Russamee, Dr. Wisanu asks to see you.
Let him in.
Hello, ma'am.
The specs of a new medical device
for your consideration.
It shouldn't be a problem.
We've worked together for a long time.
I'll let our procurement department
take care of it.
Yes.
I'm glad you're here.
I have something important to discuss.
What can I do for you?
It's not that important.
I was just wondering
if you've talked to Lada lately.
We talk on the phone sometimes.
But...
she's been busy lately
so she can't talk to me often.
This is just like you.
But I just sent her a care package.
All her favorites.
Jeez, Nu.
That's not enough.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
I have high hopes for you.
I want you to be Lada's companion.
Because one day...
Lada will come back and run this hospital.
If you marry Lada,
it will put my mind at ease.
Yes.
I'm trying to score points too.
But if it's not good enough,
I'm gonna try harder.
You can rest assured.
Studying?
The exams are coming up
but I'm still not confident.
Probably because I've been too stressed lately.
When you're stressed, look at this music box.
So you'll know you have me
by your side, always supporting you.
How adorable.
The gift giver...
or the figurine?
The figurine.
Can't compete with the gift giver.
How adorable.
Love you so much I could die.
Do you know?
You can't die.
If you die, who would I be with?
-You can't die.
You can't die.
Shall we play it?
It's my dad.
Hello, Dad.
What's wrong with Mom?
Calm down.
Earn.
Your mother's with doctors now.
But my dad told me
the tumor in her brain was very hard to treat.
that I had to prepare for the worst.
What should I do, Doc?
Don't worry.
I'll figure how a way to help your mother.
Hello, what's going on, baby?
Is this a good time to talk?
I have a big favor to ask.
Of course. What's going on?
Well,
I have a patient with a brain tumor
in critical condition.
I want her to be treated
with special care in our hospital.
Who is this patient?
She's...
a mother of my younger schoolmate.
Is this person so important
that you called me for help?
Let's just say...
you have to save her.
I'm begging you.
Of course.
What's her name?
Just give me her number. I'll take care of it.
Thank you, Mom.
I love you.
Got it.
Love you.
Love you back.
Don't worry.
Mom! Dad!
-Earn?
How did you get here? I missed you so much.
I was worried about you so I came back.
Oh, I missed you so much.
-I really did.
-Come here.
I'm not that sick.
It's nothing. Just a mass in her head.
How are you feeling? Do you get bad headaches?
Not anymore. They're not so bad now.
I actually made my peace with it.
I was gonna refuse treatment
because surgery doesn't guarantee I'll be cured.
But out of the blue
I got a call from this hospital,
telling me to get treated here.
And they said your friend arranged everything.
Plus, they had her stay in a VIP room
and got her the best doctors.
Who's your friend?
She's someone who takes care of me
while I'm over there.
She's so good to me.
I'll take it for you.
Hello?
To come down and meet who?
Hello.
You're Earn?
Yes.
Lada called me
to arrange your mother's treatment.
Yes.
She already told me.
I have to thank you.
Don't.
I did because I had to.
I read your mother's treatment history.
And I'll have a team of
my best doctors treat your mother.
But there's an understanding we must reach first.
What's that?
I know you're dating my daughter.
And I understand
we can't choose who we love.
But Lada is my best hope
and the most qualified person
to take over our hospital.
What...
What do you want me to do?
Break up with Lada.
Because the love between you and Lada
will never come to fruition.
You might be too young
to understand this.
I know my daughter.
Lada gets lonely easily.
So she found someone to be near her.
And she's well aware
that after graduation, she has to come back
and marry someone I've chosen for her.
You might be unaware
that before she went abroad,
she'd already started dating Dr. Wisanu.
FROM: WISANU P.
TO: FAHLADA T.
Doc, you've got a package from Thailand.
It says the sender is...
Mr. Wisanu. Who's that?
It's nothing.
Uh...
Let me take this call.
Hello, Nu.
Yes.
But...
she never told me.
Why would she?
You're just a toy she's having fun with.
Lada won't tell you until she graduates.
And that's the reality awaiting you.
If you break up with Lada,
I promise to give your mother the best treatment.
You have to choose
between your mother's life
and the love that's not real.
Earn!
Why didn't you tell me you were back?
I would've got you at the air...
Before she went abroad,
she'd already started dating Dr. Wisanu.
Where are you going?
I came to pack.
I'm moving back to Thailand.
Earn. Earn!
What's wrong?
Why the sudden move?
What about school?
I already transferred my credits.
I'll finish my degree there.
Doc, let go.
What's wrong?
I'm seeing someone else.
Let's break up.
Earn.
It's not true.
I wanna break up with you.
You're just a toy I've grown tired of.
Just let me go.
Earn, Earn!
Let go of me!
You're just joking around, right?
You're not really leaving, right?
You're not really leaving me, right?
I don't like women! I like men!
I like men!
Do you get it now?
And everything that happened...
What was all that?
I've been fooling you.
Because I knew you were rich.
I just wanted a comfortable life.
That's the truth.
But I can't stand it anymore.
From this day on, let's not see each other again.
Let go of me.
I won't.
Earn.
Please don't leave.
Let go of me.
-Let go of me.
-I won't!
Earn!
Let go.
Don't leave!
How could you do this to me? Let go!
Earn!
Earn! Earn! Don't leave!
Don't go, Earn!
Come back!
Earn! What did I do wrong?
Hello,
my love.
Hello, my heart.
How could you?
How could you do this to me?
Please come back, Earn.
Do you know what I wished for?
I wished for you to love me like this forever.
Will it come true?
Earn! Come back!
Is this her?
The presenter who will be
in the commercial with me?
That's right, Doctor.
This is Earn, Sanitada,
the number one rising star right now, Doctor.
If so, I'm pulling out.
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
I insist
that I really can't shoot this commercial.
Then give me a reason why you're pulling out.
I know you hate me.
Yes, I despise you.
Hello, Earn.
I've always wanted to work with you.
Let's find Lada a new girlfriend.
-Does that hurt?
-No.
You're very gentle.
Lada went through hell to get here.
Why is this brat picking at old scabs?
I'll keep coming back until you give in to me.
♪ Please don't let go of my hand ♪
♪ No matter what, please be right here ♪
♪ Having you here is reassuring ♪
♪ I'm less anxious than I used to be ♪
♪ You're the good love I never experienced ♪