(8 years ago)
Hey, baby girl!
Help! Help!
Hey, hey, hey.
-Where are you going?
Help!
-Don't hurt me. Don't hurt me.
-Come with me.
I'm begging you. Please let me go.
Hey!
Don't harass women again!
-Go!
-Let's go.
Come on.
Let's go.
Can you stand?
Are you hurt anywhere?
How will you get home?
My driver should be around here.
But my phone's dead.
Come on.
I'll help you find your car.
Cover yourself.
Your shirt is thin.
Oh! That's my car.
Thank you very much for saving me today.
My name's Ayla. What's yours?
Thank you.
Miss Jacket.
How is your owner so freaking cool?
She fought off three men.
With an umbrella like this.
How is she pretty, talented and cool?
Only one drawback.
She wouldn't tell me her name.
So how am I going to return this?
I'll probably never see her again.
So you'd better stay with me.
I'm talking to a jacket.
Hi, new kid. What's your name?
I'm Ayla.
And your first name?
Sasina.
And your last name?
Ruengkunakorn.
Hi, new friend. I'm Khaotu, Suthasinee Sawangkamol.
I've been here since Grade 7.
Nice to meet you, Ayla Sasina.
-Nice to meet...
-If you have questions, feel free to ask me
because I know everything
and everyone in this school.
But if grades stress you out,
you have nothing to worry about
because I...
get an A in every subject.
Okay, you're good.
Wanna hang out in the classroom or...
Hey!
Hey.
Khaotu.
(Don't leave this door open. Always close the door.)
Come on.
-So glad we got here in time.
-What's that?
Begin!
It's called kendo.
It's easy to follow. You score for every good hit.
You're awesome!
Wow!
-Wow!
-She's so good.
Resume play!
We've got a winner!
Hey, don't block.
-Sit down, sit down.
-Hey.
That senior.
She...
Her name is Tawan.
She's in Grade 12. An outstanding student.
The school president.
And she's our school's kendo champion.
She's a three-time champion.
Wow.
Good at school and sports?
She's good at everything.
And she's pretty.
Cool. The word is "cool."
Anyway, what club are you joining?
(Come Join the Kendo Club)
Are you really sure?
I am.
I want to join the kendo club.
But...
I think the training is very intense.
I don't think you can handle it.
I'm sure I can handle it.
I'm super ready. I'm all in.
Let's see how you do in a tryout.
Are you guys ready?
Yes!
By the look of it, that wimp won't make it.
Look at her. She's about to faint.
Let her join if she wanna join.
True.
And who's gonna train her?
I will.
You said it.
You train her.
Deal?
Deal.
All right.
Kid, no more running.
You're in.
Very good effort.
See you tomorrow at the club.
Get up and drink some water.
Hey, Tawan.
I feel lightheaded.
Are you okay?
Thank you, Tawan.
Do you remember me?
You know my name now.
This club is demanding.
Yes.
I'll try my best.
Thank you for accepting me.
Go.
Time to go home.
See you at the club tomorrow.
Ayla.
Bye-bye, Tawan!
She knows my name.
Ah!
Before we start,
I'll show you how we train kendo.
Fight! Begin!
Head! Begin!
Wrist! Begin!
Torso! Begin!
Bow!
You will start from the fundamentals.
Are you ready?
-Yes!
Kendo,
the way of the sword,
is based on the samurai swordsmanship.
To train the kendo fighting moves
that are fast, forceful and decisive,
deep concentration is required.
Come on.
Come on! Run!
Whoa!
Give us some.
Yeah, take some.
-Give me some.
-This one too.
Tawan got my gift.
She got my gift.
It's really pouring.
Tawan.
You haven't left?
Well, I forgot to bring my umbrella.
I forgot my umbrella too.
So...
why don't we find rain stoppers?
Rain stoppers?
What's that?
Let's make rain chasers.
Rain chasers?
Here.
Ooh, there's the sun. Very cool.
The sun is another word for "tawan."
Are you drawing the moon?
That's right.
Why the moon?
"Ayla" is another word for the moon.
I see.
The sun and the moon.
Tawan and Ayla.
♪ Never once did you notice ♪
♪ What my heart was feeling ♪
♪ When I look at you, my eyes say it all ♪
♪ Waiting only for you to pay me attention ♪
♪ My heart yells every day
But its voice never reaches you ♪
♪ I want you to know how long I've kept this in ♪
♪ Do you have any idea ♪
♪ As each minute goes by ♪
♪ How much my heart wants to say I love you? ♪
♪ All I know is my heart's stubborn ♪
♪ Even when you ignore me ♪
- ♪ There's pain but also love ♪
- Here we go.
♪ That has never lessened ♪
♪ The closer we are, the further it feels ♪
♪ Never once ♪
♪ Did you notice what ♪
♪ My heart was feeling ♪
♪ When I look at you ♪
- ♪ My eyes say it all ♪
- Look! The rain stops.
- ♪ Waiting only for you to pay me attention ♪
- It really works.
♪ My heart yells every day
But its voice never reaches you ♪
- ♪ I want you to know ♪
- Thank you, rain chasers.
♪ How long I've kept this in ♪
♪ Do you have any idea ♪
♪ As each minute goes by ♪
♪ How much my heart wants to say I love you? ♪
Tawan.
I'm good. Thank you.
-I'll take that.
-Tawan.
Hey.