♪ I have a heart and know how to love ♪
♪ Especially when I see you
I keep seeing the scenes ♪
♪ From when we were together ♪
♪ But I keep seeing you in my head ♪
♪ My broken heart hasn't recovered ♪
♪ So I hurt you ♪
♪ Even though I have to
Make myself watch you cry ♪
♪ I hate it but I still do it ♪
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape
But it feels like walking in circles ♪
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
♪ I try not to love you
Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
I didn’t expect my mother
to give an interview like that.
Lada, let me ask you something.
Are you never going to love a man?
I love women,
and that woman has to be Earn only.
Are you sure
you’re ready for the pressure
-that’s going to hit you out of nowhere?
-I'm ready.
How can two women truly love each other?
They can't build a proper family.
I know you're hurt,
but Lada is probably just as hurt as you.
Dear!
And Earn will be
the last most important person in my life.
Doc,
are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm not feeling unwell or anything.
Do you know
what's the hardest thing we can hide?
Our feelings.
There's no way
we can completely hide it.
It'll show itself one way or another.
You want to reconcile
with your mother, don’t you?
I think...
I’ve done so much for her already.
It's time to do things for myself.
That is enough.
If you decide to go that way,
I’ll always be by your side.
Hungry? I'll cook something for you.
Where are you going?
Well, I'm going to get something
for you to eat.
I'm not hungry,
you're not allowed to go.
Hello!
I heard that this house
has a newlywed couple.
May I join in the celebration as well?
We're not married yet.
But soon...
Perhaps?
It stinks of love.
Hey! I bought a lot of stuff.
What did you buy, Suzie?
We're having a hearty meal.
I'm not letting you go.
Let go.
You bought snacks. Won't I turn fat?
FATHER
No! Just look at me.
Father.
Hello, Father.
Your mother is experiencing
End Stage Heart Failure
and also has
Intractable Ventricular Arrhythmia.
After performing CPR for half an hour,
the vital signs kept deteriorating.
Why didn’t she ever tell me
she was sick?
She probably didn’t want you to worry.
You know her well.
Suzie.
Why do I feel so terrible?
Terrible?
About?
You didn't do anything to Doctor's mother.
But if I hadn't revealed our relationship,
if I had chosen to stay where I belong,
there'd have been no problem.
But because I chose to reveal it,
everything turned out this way.
No, dear.
Don't overthink it.
It's not a big deal, don't overthink it.
You can't stop people from being sick.
Right now,
your doctor needs a lot of encouragement.
You must not be unfaltering.
Doc.
Umm...
Doctor,
the director invites you to his room.
Lada, come and listen together.
Please continue, Doctor.
The operation was quite challenging,
but now Lady Russamee's vital signs are stable.
During the intraoperative period,
there was active bleeding,
leading to significant blood loss.
She hasn't regained consciousness yet,
possibly due to cerebral hypoxia
when her blood pressure dropped.
It's uncertain when she'll wake up
and whether she will fully recover.
During the post-operative period,
ensure there are no events that
could trigger stress for the patient,
it can potentially lead to arrhythmias
and unstable vital signs.
Yes, I understand.
You take such a long rest this time.
You usually only sleep
for a few hours, right?
Could it be that you're angry with me?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for speaking badly to you.
I'm sorry for not behaving well.
I'm sorry for...
being unable to be what you desire.
I want you to give me another chance.
Can you please wake up?
I promise to be a good girl.
Please, Mother?
I love you.
Mother,
can you hear me?
Please inform the doctor that
Lady Russamee has regained consciousness.
Yes.
Are you hungry?
Do you want coffee,
sandwiches or anything?
I'll go buy it for you.
It's alright.
I'm not hungry.
Doc.
Should we take a break for a while?
You promised not to get tired of my problems.
I've never grown tired of your problems.
However, you need to
spend most of your time with your mother.
Take the utmost care of her.
You only have one mother, after all.
I'm not going anywhere.
Whenever you take a glance back,
I'll still be inside here.
We just need to take a break
because your mother
needs you the most right now.
But this break could mean
being apart forever.
On the outside,
I may not exist in your life,
but inside here,
I am the owner of your heart.
You are the owner of my heart,
the first...
and...
the last.
♪ I have a heart and know how to love ♪
♪ Especially when I see you
I keep seeing the scenes ♪
♪ From when we were together ♪
♪ But I keep seeing you in my head ♪
♪ My broken heart hasn't recovered ♪
♪ So I hurt you... ♪
Mother.
♪ Even though I have to
Make myself watch you cry... ♪
Earn!
♪ I hate it but I still do it ♪
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape
But it feels like walking in circles ♪
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
♪ I try not to love you
Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
♪ It may seem like I don't love you
That I'm okay ♪
♪ But the truth is, inside my heart
Every time I hurt you... ♪
Lada.
♪ I feel heartbroken ♪
Mother.
♪ The pain is too much to describe ♪
♪ The more I see you sad... ♪
Are you thirsty?
♪ The more I break down ♪
I will get you some water.
Thank you, dear.
♪ But it just can't be done ♪
♪ I hate it but I still do it ♪
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape
But it feels like walking in circles ♪
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
♪ I try not to love you
Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
-Take it easy.
-Don't worry.
-Slowly, dear.
-I'm okay.
It's almost time for medicine.
I'll get the medicines for you.
Alright.
Where did that girl go?
She's gone.
Why did she suddenly...
She chose to leave...
because she knew that if she stayed,
you and Lada would fight again.
So, she chose to leave.
May I ask you directly?
Is it because of me that she became ill?
Don't blame yourself,
there's no one at fault here.
But to be honest,
Lada's mother really needs her right now.
At this moment, Lada needs to
take utmost care of her mother.
I understand.
I'll be the one to back out.
But...
won't that make you sad?
I'll be sad.
Extremely sad.
But being in love with each other...
is not enough,
we also need to understand each other.
I deeply understand her
and know how difficult it is for her.
However, if two people holding
each other's hands
are causing things to fall,
and if someone has to let go,
that person should be me.
I'm glad that...
our daughter has met someone like Earn.
She is the kind of person
who can make our daughter happy.
But she's a woman.
So?
Since our daughter loves her
and she loves our daughter,
where is the problem?
Without prejudice,
you'll be able to see
how much they love each other.
Their love is stronger than we thought.
Thank you.
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden ♪
What more do you want from me?
I chose to lay low, to be non-existent.
Is that still not enough for you?
What if I were to say that
it's still not enough?
What would you say?
Lada.
Yes, Mother?
Who is it?
Lady Russamee, hello.
I'll be direct with you.
How much do you love my daughter?
Do you know that
Lada's not just a doctor,
but she will also have to
become a director?
A director has to be responsible
for tens of thousands of people.
Are you ready to handle all that pressure
and commit to taking care of each other
until you grow old?
What more do you want from me?
I have already backed out as much as I can.
I chose to lay low, to be non-existent.
I chose to live quietly,
hidden in the narrowest corner of her heart.
I even chose to quit
the entertainment world that I love.
Do you know why?
Because I tried to do everything
in a way that would not
affect both your hearts.
I don't want to cause another problem
for your family anymore.
Is that still not enough for you?
What if I were to say that
it's still not enough?
What would you say?
I surrender.
I really surrender.
I'll accept anything...
Just don't stop me from loving her.
I am unable to do so.
When I said it wasn't enough,
what I meant was...
that I want you to...
love Lada like you used to.
Take good care of her and keep her happy.
Never let her feel sad or hurt again.
I'm sorry for underestimating the love
between the two of you in the past.
I'm sorry for thinking it was impossible.
I'm sorry.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I'm the one who brought her here.
I'm sorry, Lada.
You don't have to cry in secret anymore.
I want you to be the happiest.
Smile as much as you want.
And live the life
the two of you have dreamt of.
I'll leave her to you.
How much dowry do I have to prepare?
Don't request too much.
Mother.
Excuse me.
Don't worry about that, Mother.
We'll definitely request it.
I assure you, it'll be significant.
♪ Please don't let go of my hand ♪
♪ No matter what, please be right here ♪
♪ Having you here is reassuring ♪
♪ I'm less anxious than I used to be ♪
♪ You're the good love I never experienced ♪
Oh, so beautiful!
Both of you are so pretty!
Beautiful!
So beautiful! Fantastic!
Could you please take a photo of
me and Ms. Rose?
Sure.
With me?
Beautiful!
Oh my!
Hey, Doctor.
It's okay to not place your hand there.
Placing my hand right here is perfect.
Did you already clear
those two, three people?
Geez, Rose, that's enough.
What?
Oh, Where is Tan?
Why hasn't he arrived yet?
Oh! Over there.
He's coming over.
Dr. Tan, Dr. Wisanu.
Hey! Don't tell me that you...
Don't say a thing.
Are you guys dating?
No need to say it.
Oh!
Everyone,
something happened.
What is it?
Over there.
Someone here is feeling sad.
Heartbroken.
Don't pick on her.
Oh!
The bride is here!
♪ Please don't let go of my hand ♪
♪ No matter what, please be right here ♪
♪ Having you here is reassuring ♪
♪ I'm less anxious than I used to be ♪
♪ You're the good love I never experienced ♪
♪ I will hold your hand like this forever ♪
♪ Don't release my hand ♪
♪ Just be confident that I always have you ♪
♪ You're my one and only ♪
♪ No matter how many obstacles
I will push through ♪
♪ No matter how tough it gets ♪
♪ I want to say that I love you ♪
♪ Love you with all my heart ♪
♪ You don't need a single word ♪
♪ To tell me how much you love me ♪
♪ Your actions let me know ♪
♪ I want us to stay this way ♪
♪ No matter how tired we are ♪
♪ Our hearts are ready to fight ♪
♪ Just seeing love in our eyes ♪
♪ Is enough to make us happy ♪
♪ One thing that our hearts have for each other ♪
♪ Always constant, never changing ♪
♪ Is a bond greater than anything else ♪
♪ From today and forever ♪
♪ If someday we have to part ♪
♪ That love will not fade away ♪
♪ Love will still remain in our hearts for a long, long time ♪
♪ You don't need a single word ♪
♪ To tell me how much you love me ♪
♪ Your actions let me know ♪
♪ I want us to stay this way ♪
♪ No matter how tired we are ♪
♪ Our hearts are ready to fight ♪
♪ Just seeing love in our eyes ♪
♪ Is enough to make us happy ♪
It's fine even if it's not completed.
No need to stress over it.
But this is our home.
Here, this is our home.
But it's not completed.
Not everything has to be
perfect and completed.
Doc!
It's completed.
It's beyond completed.
Are you ready?
Ready for what?
Honeymoon.
I'm ready.
This is our home?
That's right, that's our home.
Thank you!
Here.
This way, my lady.
Thank you!
Should I place our photo here?
Is it a good idea? Here.
Good idea.
Hello,
my love.
Hello, my heart.
I'm so happy, my love.
For calling me that,
I doubt we'll get to return to Thailand.
That's not okay.
You have to return and manage the hospital
as Mother instructed.
Geez.
I am out of favor already.
This is the new favorite daughter, I suppose.
Certainly.
Doc.
Yes?
I want to thank you
for doing this much for me.
I can do even more for you.
Would you like me to prove it?
I love you,
my little rascal.
♪ I will hold your hand like this forever ♪
♪ Don't release my hand ♪
♪ Just be confident that I always have you ♪
♪ You're my one and only ♪
♪ No matter how many obstacles
I will push through ♪
♪ No matter how tough it gets ♪
♪ I want to say that I love you ♪
♪ Love you with all my heart ♪
♪ You don't need a single word ♪
♪ To tell me how much you love me ♪
♪ Your actions let me know ♪
♪ I want us to stay this way ♪
♪ No matter how tired we are ♪
♪ Our hearts are ready to fight ♪
♪ Just seeing love in our eyes ♪
♪ Is enough to make us happy ♪
♪ One thing that our hearts have for each other ♪
♪ Always constant, never changing ♪
♪ Is a bond greater than anything else ♪
♪ From today and forever ♪
♪ If someday we have to part ♪
♪ That love will not fade away ♪
♪ Love will still remain in our hearts for a long, long time ♪
♪ You don't need a single word ♪
♪ To tell me how much you love me ♪
♪ Your actions let me know ♪
♪ I want us to stay this way ♪
♪ No matter how tired we are ♪
♪ Our hearts are ready to fight ♪
♪ Just seeing love in our eyes ♪
♪ Is enough to make us happy ♪
♪ You don't need a single word ♪
♪ Your actions let me know ♪
♪ I want us to stay this way ♪
♪ No matter how tired we are ♪
♪ Our hearts are ready to fight ♪
♪ Just seeing love in our eyes ♪
♪ Is enough to make us happy ♪