I have something for you.
Hm?
What's that?
(Dance and Drama Club, audition for dancers
to compete in the annual contest)
You want me to compete?
Yes.
I want you to apply.
Think of it as a test of your ability.
But will I make it?
There are many seniors
who are good dancers in the club.
Come on.
Give it a try.
What's the harm?
Think of it as gaining experience.
All right.
I'll apply.
So on the day of the contest,
will you come and cheer for me?
I think that's doable.
Promise?
Promise.
Don't break your promise.
(Dance and Drama Club, audition)
Promise with a thumb stamp.
Ayla!
Tawan!
I thought you wouldn't make it.
I'm sorry for being late.
I got tied up with something.
It's okay. I'm just glad you made it.
I'm feeling so encouraged.
I couldn't possibly break my promise.
Hey.
What happened to your lips?
Just a small accident.
I'm okay.
Wait a sec.
I have some ointment on me.
Here.
You have it on you at all times?
I do. I must have it on me
at all times because I'm clumsy.
Here. I'll put it on you.
So you won't get a scar.
I'm done.
Here.
Keep it and apply it at home.
So you won't get a scar, okay?
Hello, Khaotu?
Oh, okay.
I'm coming.
Okay.
I have to go and prepare.
Please wait for my routine.
Ayla.
I want you to have it.
The school lapel pin?
But you haven't graduated.
Use it as a lucky charm.
Thank you.
Ayla!
(Thailand Passport)
I have a confession to make.
Thank you for always being there
and taking care of me.
The snacks I left in your locker
were my small thanks to you.
I'm so happy I attend the same school as you
and get to know you.
One last thing,
I love you.
I hope
it's mutual.
Why are you napping here, kid?
I came to see Tawan.
Where is she?
Hasn't she told you?
Told me what?
Well, she moved to another school.
Moved?
Do you have her address?