♪ I have a heart and know how to love ♪
♪ Especially when I see you
I keep seeing the scenes ♪
♪ From when we were together ♪
♪ But I keep seeing you in my head ♪
♪ My broken heart hasn't recovered ♪
♪ So I hurt you ♪
♪ Even though I have to
Make myself watch you cry ♪
♪ I hate it but I still do it ♪
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape
But it feels like walking in circles ♪
♪ In the end I hurt myself
Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden
I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
♪ I try not to love you
Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
I used to date the doctor.
Used to date?
Don't tell me that
you've reconnected with
your old flame last night?
Serving the food before
the guest even arrives.
I’ve ordered your
favorite food in advance.
Fried boiled egg
with tamarind sauce, my favorite.
What do you want?
I’m courting Earn,
please cheer me on.
Are you only here
to find the cell phone?
Why do I have to stay?
Just accompany me.
Unless you’re afraid
of your own feelings.
Why bother with all the effort to cook?
I don't want to eat with you.
Okay.
Make way, please.
Fine, I'll taste it for you.
I can tell it's not delicious.
It's not tasty at all. Bland.
Is it really that delicious?
Not delicious.
Your expression, though.
I said it's not delicious.
It's not delicious.
You don't have to eat it.
-I wasn't going to eat it anyway.
-You don't have to eat it.
I wasn't going to eat it anyway.
I said I'm not eating...
Eat.
It's hard.
I've been working on this for ages
and still can't do it.
Wow!
I've been at it for so long.
This piece.
Here.
Oh, wow.
Let me see.
What?
That's not it.
-It is!
-How could there be a pink piece here?
I told you it doesn't fit.
It doesn't fit.
Here.
A jigsaw piece.
Yes.
For me to complete?
Uh-huh.
And what picture is it?
Do you have a reference for me to see?
-It's a secret.
-A secret?
Can someone like me complete it?
Even with a reference,
I still can't do it.
You can complete it.
You can do it.
And after you finish it,
you'll see that this picture is
very important for our relationship.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Look at this. This is my dream house.
I dream that one day
I'll own this house.
This
must be expensive.
Doctor,
is this
our house?
I'm heading back.
What's going on?
Doctor.
Doctor!
Drive safely,
my love.
What are you doing, Lada?
Stay focused!
Losing again and again.
Lada!
New lipstick, right?
It looks nice.
Did you hear that?
I'm not imagining things, right?
Confirmed.
She still remembers I like white lilies.
So good at making up.
Do you like them, Lada?
When I bought them,
I just thought they looked pretty.
But if you like them, I'm happy.
These are from you, Nu?
Thank you.
You have another patient appointment
this evening, right?
So, please have coffee with me.
Then please
let me pack up my things
for about five minutes.
Sure.
FRIENDS
SOS. I NEED URGENT HELP
Here you go.
But usually I see you
drinking black coffee.
Why did you drink orange juice today?
Oh,
I've run out of my coffee quota.
I only have one glass per day.
Ah okay,
I'll note this down then.
Then please note down my details too.
I drink less sweetened cappuccino
in case I gain weight.
Less sweetened cappuccino
to avoid gaining weight?
But you also drink boba tea
and sweet Chinese Pastry,
I guess it's not fat at all?
-And what about you...
-Enough!
How long are you all
going to argue over my head?
Sit down. Sit.
You're doing fine right, Bow, Mr. Tan?
Whenever I come here
I always see you two together.
Ah, you see,
we just happen to be quite close,
the three of us.
We always go places together.
Bow,
is my order ready yet?
Hello.
Pardon me?
Is it an emergency case?
How is the patient?
Okay, I'll hurry over now.
Should I give you
the Golden Globe Award?
I've done my job,
you figure out how
to escape by yourself.
Please excuse me.
Sure.
Take care then.
Uh oh!
Oh, it's my cell phone.
Oh my god, you need me?
Oh, okay, I'll hurry over now.
Hey,
I have to go too.
Sure.
Please excuse me.
Normally the skin doctors emergencies
happen every day?
Uhh...
You see...
Your americano is ready.
I'll get it for you.
It's okay, I'll get it myself.
No, it's fine, it's nothing.
It's okay, I ordered it.
It's really okay!
-It's no problem.
-I'll get it for you.
-Really it's fine.
-No, it's okay.
Whoa!
Ugh!
Oh no!
My apologies.
I'm sorry.
You can go change into my shirt first
and you can return it later.
Thank you.
I can do it myself.
It's okay, I'm a doctor.
Did you forget
that I'm a doctor
too?
You're right.
Here you go.
I'll wash and return it to you.
Okay.
What got into me?
Good morning, everyone.
We're here!
Hey,
she bought everything at the market.
Amazing, Mother.
Distribute this, even give some to Wang.
He eats a lot. Give these to him.
Oh, that's too much.
I haven't picked anything yet.
-Let me choose first.
-Mother.
You need to be nourished.
Here, take this.
Here.
Wow.
Eat it all, okay?
Oh, let's eat together later.
Come.
You sit and do your makeup first.
How are you?
You seem to be in a good mood today.
When good things happen,
you should be in a good mood, right?
So, if good things happen,
I hope you won't forget about me.
Whatever you want,
just tell me,
and I'll take care of it for you.
Really?
Yes.
But I don't want money or sweets.
Kiss me on the cheek as a reward.
Do you want it like
in the drama or in real life?
In real life.
Hey!
Are my nails pretty?
Your nails are very pretty, sis.
What are you doing?
Just teasing.
Oh,
teasing.
You're teasing too much.
She's just been weaned.
Weaned!
-Weaned!
Let's change clothes.
I'll be right back.
I'll take her to change clothes.
Sure.
Which one, Mother?
-Hey!
-Earn!
Cut, cut, cut!
Ratee!
Check on her.
Tell me if you're hurt anywhere.
My leg.
Hey.
Did you mess up the cue again, Ratee?
I didn't mean to.
How was I supposed to know
this would happen?
I don't believe you.
We practiced the cue already.
What's this?
Are you afraid of the effects?
You fell and hit Earn.
If it wasn't intentional,
what do you call that?
I call it bad luck.
I was working just fine,
and something happened.
Want to know what that something is?
I can arrange it for you.
Geez.
You hurt someone else
and still don't feel guilty.
Isn't this going too far?
Stop.
-Why?
-Or you won't get to breathe again.
-Bring it on!
Calm down, everyone.
Ratee,
even if it wasn't intentional,
you messed up the cue.
Look, your friend is hurt,
and I haven't heard
a single apology from you.
Sorry.
Hey, why not wait until the next life?
What good is it saying it now?
Ugh, everything I do is wrong.
-Should I withdraw?
-Yes, withdraw.
Withdraw then,
someone who messes up 30, 40 takes,
just withdraw.
Go ahead!
Suzie.
I'm fine now.
Help her up.
Can you get up?
So high-maintenance.
Take it slowly, be careful.
What?
Blood!
Take her to the hospital right away.
Suzie, go!
Let's go.
Oh no.
Move out of the way!
So chaotic.
Earn.
Are you alright?
This way.
Family members are not allowed to enter.
But I'm worried about her.
-Please, let us and check on her.
-Please, let us go in.
I'm sorry, but it's really against
our hospital's policy.
Family members must wait outside.
Please.
Doctor.
Please calm down.
I will take care of her.
Then, please take care of her for us.
This way please.
Doctor.
Prepare the stitching equipment.
Yes, Doctor.
It's okay.
I'll give you a local anesthetic.
It will hurt a little.
Just a little.
Like an ant bite.
Very good.
Don't cry.
I'll make the stitches nice and neat.
Just a little.
Just a little more and it will be done.
Does it hurt?
It still hurts a little.
But I want to keep feeling this way.
Why?
So you'll pay attention to me.
Hmm?
Oh!
Earn, how are you?
I'm better. I can run by tomorrow.
Doctor,
will there be a scar?
If she follows my instructions,
there won't be.
Just don't go out drinking at night.
It might make it worse.
I heard that when you were abroad,
you and Earn stayed in the same place?
Did Earn say that?
Who do you think I heard it from?
Did Earn tell you
what kind of relationship we had?
Yes.
She said you were "friends."
Doctor,
doctor!
Doctor!
Engfah,
I think this has gone too far.
I never said that,
and I never told you
anything about abroad.
Where did you hear that from?
I...
It was me.
Okay, okay, I didn't mean it.
Are you worried about the doctor?
Yes,
she has a quick temper and
it's hard for her to calm down.
That's why it was fun teasing her.
Eng!
Okay, I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
No,
I'll try not to do it again, okay?
Don't be mad.
I'm sorry.
Let's head back.
Excuse me, we're leaving now.
I'm sorry.
Please, don't be mad at me.
I didn't mean it.
How is the new cream I gave you?
Any allergies?
No allergies.
The cream is very smooth.
It absorbs quickly and isn't sticky.
Then let me see, please.
Continue using this cream.
I'll prescribe a new one,
Redeno cream.
You can use them together.
Thank you.
One moment, doctor.
Take your time.
Hello, Engfah.
Eating with whom?
Earn?
The two of you can eat.
Don’t feel obliged to invite me.
Okay.
Bye.
They just left the hospital
and are already out having
a romantic meal together.
Geez,
they're afraid it'll look bad,
so they wanted me to be a buffer.
Earn is always like that.
She flirts with everyone she's near.
The hashtag "Charming Manager"
is fitting.
If possible,
I wish you could see them on set
and see how Engfah and Earn
are so sweet together.
Then you'd know what I know.
Real kisses, no stand-ins.
Don’t believe me?
I have pictures.
Here.
Not just a picture,
I have a video too, if you want to see.
Doctor.
What’s it going to be?
Hmm?
What do you mean?
I asked what’s it going to be!
What are you talking about?
I don’t understand.
Stop pretending to be stupid.
Is this fun for you?
Do you think I’m that stupid,
so you can just mess with me?
Mess with you?
I’ve never messed with you.
And if you’re talking about Engfah,
I’ve never thought of her that way.
The only person I love
and have always loved is you!
I want to build a family with you!
Family.
Family, right?
Fine.
Doctor, what are you doing...
Here, this is family.
Why are you doing this?
Don’t you know that
I considered this
a symbol of our feelings getting back
to what they were?
Yeah.
Back to what they were.
Back to what they were, indeed.
Back to lying to me!
Pretending to be good,
and then lying again,
playing with my feelings.
Or
is the money not enough?
How much do you want?
For that night,
or should it be tonight?
♪ In the end I hurt myself ♪
♪ Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden ♪
♪ I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
Earn.
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
♪ I try not to love you ♪
♪ Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
♪ It may seem like I don't love you ♪
♪ That I'm okay ♪
Earn.
♪ But the truth is, inside my heart, every time I hurt you ♪
Suzie!
♪ The pain is too much to describe ♪
I can't take this anymore!
I give up!
I surrender to her!
Earn. Calm down.
♪ Erase the memories of when we were in love ♪
♪ But it just can't be done ♪
When this drama is over,
I won't stay here anymore!
Earn!
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape ♪
♪ But it feels like walking in circles ♪
♪ In the end I hurt myself ♪
♪ Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden ♪
I can't handle this anymore!
Look at what she did!
Why did she treat me like this?
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
Earn.
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
♪ I try not to love you ♪
♪ Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
My love.
♪ I hate it but I still do it ♪
♪ I keep picking at scabs to hurt you ♪
♪ I want to escape ♪
♪ But it feels like walking in circles ♪
Earn.
♪ In the end I hurt myself ♪
♪ Keeping my love hidden ♪
Earn.
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden ♪
♪ I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
Being deceived repeatedly...
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
...means you never learn.
But still hurting yourself like this...
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
...it's called being "stupid."
♪ I try not to love you ♪
♪ Holding back my tears while saying goodbye ♪
♪ But I could never do it for real ♪
Is she really leaving the industry?
What happened, Suzie?
Dr. Fahlada.
I'm sorry,
I have to get back to work.
No time to chat.
Scared, huh?
If you're scared and trying to
avoid problems like this,
be my guest.
Whatever's on your mind,
just hurry up and say it
don't waste my time.
I want you and Earn to reconcile.
How's that?
Is it fast enough for you?
It's none of your business.
Yes it is,
I'm the one who caused
you two to quarrel.
It's my responsibility
to reconcile you both.
Not necessary,
because I don't want to see
that woman's face again.
Okay.
Then,
I'll seriously court Earn.
That's your business,
why are you telling me?
Then why are you getting angry?
Previously,
I was going to court Earn.
I was serious about it.
But Earn doesn't like me
because she loves you.
If you're still hesitating
or doubting Earn,
think about
what flaws I might have
that Earn wouldn't open her heart to.
If it's not that Earn
only has you in her heart.
Dr. Fahlada,
someone may have many people
come into their life,
but to love someone more than yourself
happens only once.
If you let it slip away,
it's like never finding
your other half for life.
Think about the rest yourself, okay?
And I also have another question
I want to ask you.
Who made you so angry
that you had to take it out on Earn?
I may have been the cause,
but if no one fueled the fire,
you probably wouldn't have
acted that way towards Earn.
Who was it?
This is clearly a cover-up of murder.
Cut!
Alright, got it.
Moving on to the next scene.
Okay, Ratee.
Your scenes for today are done.
Yes! Then I'll head home now.
Sure.
You know, May wanted to
get laid so badly that she cheated with
a guy 10 years younger than her,
despite him dating someone.
But since she's the queen bee,
she shamelessly stole him just like that.
No, there's more.
She wanted the guy so badly
that she became pregnant,
in the end the guy left her
and she got abortion.
This is the number one heroine.
Disgu--
Eng.
I feel sorry for you.
You tried to back stab your colleague,
but someone managed to
get hold of the audio clip
and it's in my hands now.
Someone like you
probably doesn't even know
the meaning of true friendship.
What do you want?
Don't mess with Earn
and Dr. Fahlada anymore.
Who are you to order me around like this?
Ask something smarter.
You already heard the voice clip.
Don't you get it yet,
why I dare to order you?
Do you realize yet that
even though May may fall,
she still gets along with the organizers
and has enough connections
in the industry
to make you fall.
I made Earn and the doctor quarreled.
You also benefited.
Why are you doing this?
I don't want this kind of awful benefit.
I've cleared things up
with the doctor already.
I hope I don't have to clear
things up a second time.
Otherwise,
you'll have to prepare to answer
May's questions and
the world of social media.
I love you
and I'll do everything
to make you love me again.
There's no going back
to how things were,
Ms. Sanitada.
But I want to see you every day.
That's your problem.
My problem is figuring out
how to get you out of my life for good.
You lost me a long time ago.
There hasn't been a single day
where I haven't thought of you.
Save your lies
for someone else.
Doctor, no, please.
Doctor,
I'm sorry,
I was wrong.
Can you give me another chance?
I won't make the same mistake twice.
I'll love you more than ever,
and I won't make you sad again.
Get out of my life
and don't come back.
Doctor!
Can you come back?
Doctor, please come back.
♪ In the end I hurt myself ♪
♪ Keeping my love hidden ♪
♪ I can't walk away even if I want to ♪
♪ My love must be hidden ♪
♪ I can hardly stand it ♪
♪ It's torture when you cry ♪
♪ The more you're hurt ♪
♪ The weaker my heart becomes ♪
Father,
I'm going to shoot the commercial
as you suggested.
If I really wanted to pressure you,
I'd have arranged the marriage ages ago.
If the heart isn't in it, it just isn't.
Hey, I thought Fahlada said
she wasn't going to return.
I've wanted to do this for a long time.
In front of others,
I was afraid you'd be embarrassed.
Afraid I'd be embarrassed
or are you just not brave enough?
After I helped your mother,
you repay me by turning against me
and breaking your promise?
I love the doctor.
That's why today,
I’m taking back my love.
♪ Please don't let go of my hand ♪
♪ No matter what, please be right here ♪
♪ Having you here is reassuring ♪
♪ I'm less anxious than I used to be ♪
♪ You're the good love I never experienced ♪