Am I in your sight now?
Please sign.
Do you have a pen?
♪ You are the moon in my heart ♪
♪ You make everything ♪
(The protected VIP)
♪ More meaningful every day ♪
♪ I wanna be your sun ♪
(Dance and Drama Club)
Promise with a thumb stamp.
♪ Please let me ♪
♪ Be by your side and keep on loving you ♪
♪ You bring light to the darkness ♪
♪ You make me smile every day ♪
♪ You make the lonely nights ♪
Promise with a thumb stamp.
♪ Once looked lonely ♪
♪ They're now filled with your shadow ♪
♪ As the light to my heart ♪
♪ You are the moon in my heart ♪
(Bodyguard)
♪ You make everything ♪
♪ More meaningful every day ♪
♪ I wanna be your sun ♪
I'm gonna put the rules away.
Then we'll go to my office.
Yes, Ms. Ayla.
It's Ayla.
Can you call me Ayla like you used to?
I'm afraid I can't, Ms. Ayla.
Rule 27:
Obey the VIP's orders as long as they're not lethal.
Calling me Ayla isn't lethal, is it, Tawan?
Huh?
Sure.
Ayla.
♪ Know that the person you're gazing ♪
♪ Is not so easily charmed by you ♪
♪ Know that I'm a superstar ♪
♪ Eh, eh, eh, eh, eh ♪
♪ Who wants in have to wait their turns ♪
♪ I'm not a snob, I'm just not so chilled ♪
♪ If I date someone, they need good reviews ♪
♪ Hey, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Only you ♪
♪ I'm not bragging ♪
♪ But I love you too ♪
♪ I have to act tough ♪
Over here, Ayla!
-Hello.
-Are you doing well?
-I am.
-I missed you.
-You got prettier.
I'm gonna go, guys. Goodbye.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, stand alone ♪
♪ Know that I'm number one ♪
♪ I must be placed at the top ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, stand alone ♪
♪ Know that I'm number one ♪
♪ I must be placed at the top ♪
What?
Hello, boss?
What's up, Chanya?
Give me a sec.
Eh?
Is something wrong?
Sorry, do you mind turning around for me?
Do you mind doing this move?
And do you mind vocalizing like this?
Are you interested in auditioning tomorrow?
I'm not.
Eh? Why not?
You're good-looking and have a great body.
You're perfect to be an artist.
Or are you insecure about singing?
Don't worry about that. We can train you.
Well...
I'm here
to take care of Ms. Ayla.
Ki, we hired someone to take care of Ayla?
Why haven't I been informed?
We didn't. I have to ask Tik.
Tell Tik for find someone else.
As for this beautiful girl,
I'll have her debut as an artist.
Huh? Debut as an artist?
Boss.
That won't do.
This beautiful lady is my personal bodyguard.
Her name is Rawee.
A bodyguard?
I don't mind. It's totally okay.
If she becomes famous after her debut,
I'm willing to give you a cut.
Please. So pretty.
That won't do.
I'm very protective of her.
Well...
That's understandable.
She's really beautiful.
I just finished recording the rap verse. Wanna listen?
-Let's listen to it. I did my best.
-All right, all right.
And I wanted to talk to you about the bloody doll.
What actually happened there, boss?
What were you gonna say, Chanya?
Chanya.
Yes, boss.
I have something to report.
We've received information on the bloody doll.
There are fingerprints inside the box
and I'm having Nana look into them.
But the blood on the doll
isn't human blood, but animal blood,
and it contains nothing dangerous.
Email me if you get more details.
Copy that.
Oh, boss?
How's the job...
How's the job been for you?
Nothing to report.
I just haven't approved the bonuses.
Bonuses?
Boss, I actually wasn't curious at all.
Nana and Typhoon were pestering me to ask you.
-I'm not involved.
-I was never...
Hey, Ya, don't do that. That's not true.
Stop, stop, stop.
-I didn't say anything, boss.
-Don't talk. Be quiet.
I'm gonna go.
Hello. Good evening, guys.
-Good evening.
- You're so pretty. Are you tired?
I'm not. Are you guys tired?
-Not at all.
-Thank you so much for coming today.
-Please get a lot of rest.
-I will. You too.
-See you.
-I will. Goodbye.
Jam, please drop me off at the Sathon place today.
Yes, you got it, miss.
The Sathon place?
That's right. I live in two places.
This one is for when I get off work late. It's closer.
All by yourself?
All by myself.
But don't worry.
Mr. Thana approved its safety.
My dad chose it himself.
We passed on a dozen places before finding this one.
Oh, he didn't like any place I showed him back then.
"This one's too big. This one's too small.
The kitchen's too small. You'll trip and fall."
When we agreed on this one, I almost set off fireworks.
He's very protective of you.
He is. We only have each other.
My dad's super protective of me.